In the beginning,
the universe was in perfect balance,
kept in peace and harmony
by four magic books.
The Alliance of Evil Wizards
made it their mission
to capture these books
and shroud the universe in darkness.
One of the books,
called Jaunty Grimoire, got away.
That's me! Cha-cha-cha!
- Ze magic book!
- Where is it?
Find it at once!
She was rescued by
a group of mighty blue guardians.
Those evil wizards won't get you.
I've got her, Ron.
You're safe with us, little one.
They swore to protect the magic book.
The fate of the universe depended on it.
So they hid her away in a secret location.
Now shh! Don't tell anyone.
I'm in Smurf Village!
La, la, la-la-la-la
Sing a happy song
Smurf the whole day long!
La, la, la-la-la-la
Sing a happy song
Check this out.
Everybody know
What we came to do
Everybody here
Want a chance with you
You know that's your cousin
And your brother
And the trees and the bees
And the birds
Want to dance with you
But I heard you were
Feeling blue
I don't know
If you're feeling cute
But you're looking
So put-together
I just started feeling cool
You gots to coordinate
I match with you--
Red, green and gray
I'm still here
We got mass appeal
Whatever color you feel Because
Everything goes with blue
It look good On me, good on you
Butter-fly in that suit
Everything goes with blue
I look in the sky, I see you
You're a star Bright and blue
Everything goes with blue!
You gots to coordinate
I match with you--
Red, green and gray
I'm still here
We got mass appeal
Come on, No Name.
Everything goes with blue
It looks, it looks
Good on me, good on you
Butter-fly in that suit
Everything goes with blue
I look in the sky I see you
You're a star Bright and blue
Everything goes with...
Ha! Now that's what I call a banger!
Great job, Smurfs!
Yay for us!
A few timing issues,
but you almost had it this time, No Name.
Same time, same place tomorrow!
Adding it to the calendar, Papa Smurf.
Thank you, Calendar Smurf.
Isn't it grand
living in a place
where everyone has a thing!
Excuse me?
You stepped in it now, Papa.
Papa Smurf! Quick follow-up, if I may.
And here we go.
I still don't have a "thing."
And a quick follow-up to the follow-up:
Don't you think that that's a bit odd?
Like, Hefty Smurf is hefty.
I smash things.
And Worry Smurf worries.
You know, maybe everybody else
just doesn't worry enough.
And Brainy is...
really smart.
- And Grouchy is...
- Don't even say it.
And there's Camouflage Smurf.
I'm right here.
Out-of-Focus Smurf. Clumsy Smurf.
Way-Back-There Smurf.
I'm way over here.
Handlebar Moustache Smurf.
Quiet Smurf.
- What did he say?
- I have no idea.
But do you see what I'm saying, Papa?
Well, you're No Name. That's a thing.
Is it, though?
'Cause if my thing is
my distinct absence of a thing,
I'm actually...
nothing.
Hey, Sound Effect Smurf, can you back off?
Even he's got a thing.
And he's only been here since Tuesday.
I wouldn't worry
about it too much, No Name.
Some Smurfs just take a little more time
to find their thing.
It's in there.
You just got to find a way to let it out.
I've been thinking.
We don't have a Magic Smurf around here.
Maybe that could be my thing.
Smurfs can't do magic.
But I'm sure there's
something else for you.
Hey, List-Making Smurf.
What's left on our giant list of
Things-to-Try-to-Find-
No-Name-a-Name list?
Well, let's see, Papa.
Okay, to date we've tried...
10,248 things.
How many do we have left?
Two. Clog making and...
shark taming.
Well, that's wonderful news!
Let's try clog making.
That's a great idea, Papa Smurf.
Right, Smurfs?
Yeah!
I guess I could learn to like clogs.
Just take your time, No Name.
Don't rush it.
I'll just be right here. You got this.
If you could make something
with a square toe,
that'd be great. Thanks.
- Aw.
- Terrible clog!
You know, there's always shark taming.
That one's already taken.
That's too bad.
Hey, I have a great idea!
Let's go pick some Smurfberries.
It's hard to feel bad
with a sack full of Smurfberries.
I must admit, Smurfette,
there is a gnawing emptiness inside me
that all the Smurfberries
in the land couldn't fill.
It's hard to be the odd Smurf out.
I think I might know a little something
about that feeling.
What do you mean?
Well, I'm the only Smurf
created out of a block of clay
by our mortal enemy,
the evil wizard Gargamel,
in the hopes of luring
all Smurfs to their doom.
I mean, that was a lot for me to process.
So how do you handle that, Smurfette?
Well, I just think about all the friends
who love me and that I love back.
And I get the strength
to keep on keeping on.
You'll find your thing, No Name.
So don't give up.
Thanks, Smurfette. I cherish us.
I cherish us too... infinity!
I cherish you infinity times
infinity plus one.
It's not a competition.
But if it was, I'd cherish you
infinity times infinity
plus one times pi times infinity,
and I'd win.
Smurfette's right.
I need to stop dwelling
on what I don't have
and start dwelling on what I do.
But why is that so hard for me?
Who am I?
Where do I belong?
Heavy heart, but I carry on
Searching for the answers
But I'm only Moving backwards
What they say
When they think of me
Does a name Tell you anything?
Does happy ever after
Ever really happen?
I'm always on the outside
Looking in
Never finding nothing
I'm always on the sidelines
In the end
And you only see The downside
When you're always
On the outside
I try to find
A reason to be strong
I'm holding on For something
But no one ever knows
What's going on
'Cause you keep it On the inside
When you're always
On the outside
Always on the outside
When you're always
On the outside looking in
Looking in
I need a chance
To prove them all wrong
And see the world
From the side I never walk on
I know there's
Something there for me
I still believe
I wish I had my own thing.
Aw, poor thing.
It's in you. You just need a little help.
What's happening?
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
Hallelujah
What the shell?
Sorry!
Quick question: What's going on?
Well, I wished for a thing and...
You got magic!
Smurfette!
Papa Smurf! Papa Smurf!
You seem to have a bee in your bonnet.
What's on your mind, No Name?
It took 10,248 tries, but I did it.
I finally found my thing.
Well, that's fantastic! What is it?
I know you said Smurfs can't do magic.
But I can.
It's the thing I really wanted!
Wait, what are you talking about?
He never stopped trying to find his thing
and I'm so proud.
Show him!
Okay, let's see...
Va-va-voom!
That's what I'm talking about!
Stop!
Sire, it's Joel! It's Joel!
We found Smurf Village!
Smurf Village?
Wonderful, Joel! How did we do that?
There was an energy pulse detected
on our energy-pulse detector.
Shall I send in your brother?
Gargamel? Absolutely not.
That imbecile will only get in the way.
Just initiate extraction measures.
Yes, Lord Razamel. Most evil.
What is that?
He found us.
There's so much I didn't tell you.
Your Smurf location hath been acquired!
Everyone, listen to me!
Your lives are in terrible danger!
Smurf Village isn't safe anymore!
We have an emergency plan
in case this very thing happened.
Find Ken.
Finekin? What does that mean?
Find Ken!
Oh, no, Papa's gone!
Who will protect us now?
Why?
Wait, wait! Everybody calm down.
We need to be rational here.
There's only one evil wizard
who would do this.
Gargamel.
No Name, use your magic to find Gargamel.
That is not your greatest idea.
I just got Papa Smurfnapped!
Just focus. Concentrate.
Okay. Gargamel. Gargamel. Gargamel.
Success!
My sweet Azrael, what sound do you think
a Smurf makes right before he expires?
That's the sound I imagined, too.
You're such a delight, my furry angel.
- Gargamel!
- Yes?
Did you just speak human, Azrael?
Show thyself!
It's Smurf Village.
Oh, no, not the evil wizard Gargamel.
Look, Azrael, a poor abandoned Smurf.
Let's smoosh it.
Ha-ha. Sucker.
All right, Gargamel. Spill the beans.
- What did you do with Papa?
- Papa? Nothing!
Release me from this cage at once!
Something tells me you're
not telling us everything.
You got Papa snatched.
If I had Papa Smurf,
I'd be gloating about it right now.
Well, maybe we should give him
a makeover he'll never forget.
- Hey, Smurfs!
- Hey, Clumsy.
Guys!
Is this--
Is this any--
It's just--
Didn't Papa say to find Ken?
"Spin this track from beginning to end.
Through this portal you'll find Ken."
- Thank you, Clumsy.
- You're welcome.
No Name,
this is how we're gonna get Papa back.
Let's do it.
This is not going to end well.
I hate being eaten by a grammy-phone.
Run away!
What's happening?
We're obviously in some kind
of non-Newtonian portal.
Where is it taking us?
To the land of Ken.
Smurfette?
I'm here! Hefty?
Here! Worry?
Here. Brainy?
Present. Vanity?
Here! Grouchy?
Here. Unfortunately.
Where are all the mushrooms
and Smurfberries?
Where are we?
It's Paris.
How do you know that, Smurfette?
Je ne sais pas.
- Je ne sais what now?
- I'm not really sure.
Let's just stick to the plan.
Find Ken, save Papa.
Let's go, Smurfs.
And Turtle.
And Turtle. Sorry.
Hello, fellow wizard members
of the Evil Alliance.
We cannot hear you.
Oopsies. Sorry, I was just...
I was inquiring:
- Did you all have fun weekends?
- Cut the codswallop, Razamel!
We can't link our four books together,
erase all goodness and shroud the universe
in a cloud of Dark Magic forever
if we only have three books!
That's just Logic 101.
Yes, and I feel terrible about that,
and that's why I'm super excited
to share some great news with the council.
You have your magic book?
Well, no, not that great.
But I am so close.
He says that every time, you know?
It's been 106 years!
And Razamel,
how much longer
do we have to wait for you?
Do we need to replace you, Razamel?
- No! Please, no!
- Sire, a word?
Joel, I'm on a very important Zoom.
It's them, sire.
- Who them?
- The them.
Quick bathroom break, ladies and gents.
Thank you!
We're one step closer
to total evil dominance!
Huzzah for the bad guys!
Huzzah, I say!
Yes, sire. Huzzah, indeed.
Why did we design the Zoom room
so far away from my evil lair, Joel?
Well, that's where
your laptop is, my lord.
My podcast microphones are set up
in the Zoom room, Joel!
Why wouldn't I use my podcast
microphones for my Zooms?
Yes! Papa!
One hundred years in the making.
He hid, I seeked, and I won!
You've won nothing, Razamel.
Oh, really?
Who's in a jar in my evil lair?
- Where's the book?
- Shoot.
I don't know. I saw Papa,
and I grabbed him.
Maybe it's in his pocket?
Look at him, Joel.
He's... He's the size of
a slice of apple pie.
Would a book fit
into a miniature man's pockets, Joel?
Honestly, it would depend
on how big his pants were.
Go back from whence you grabbed him
and find that book! Now!
Yes, sire.
It's good to see you, Papa Smurf.
I cannot say the same.
I've got something!
In the same portal
that picked up Papa Smurf.
Seize it, Joel!
Bring that magic book back to me.
Yes... yes... yes!
What is this wretched place?
Gargamel?
Razamel, you found me!
I knew you wouldn't leave your own brother
stranded forever!
I missed you so much!
Yes, yes. Reunited, and it feels so good.
And you're the one who took Papa Smurf.
Well, all right, all right.
Well done, baby bro.
Too bad you didn't
get the rest of the Smurfs.
And you never will.
My Smurfs are hidden away,
safe and secure.
What did you do, Hefty?
I just asked 'em where Ken was!
I don't think they speak Smurf.
Don't bite my face!
Actually, a dog's bark
is worse than its bite.
This way!
Watch out!
It's a killer brush death machine!
I'm a bird! A beautiful bird.
- Who are these guys?
- City Smurfs.
Salut! My name's Moxie.
And we're the lnternational
Neighborhood Watch Smurfs.
Paris Division.
- That sounds important.
- It is.
What kind of Smurfs are you?
We are...
the standard kind.
Smurf Village Division.
Smurf Village? Where's Papa?
That's why we're here.
He told us to find Ken.
We'll take you to him.
We got you. Follow us. Hup, hup, hup.
Ken's inside the discotheque.
Get across the dance floor.
Avoid feet!
Come on!
- Almost there.
- Almost where?
There!
See you on the other side.
So, where's Ken?
I'm right here.
Let me guess. Papa Smurf's in trouble.
- How did you know that?
- I'm Papa Smurf's brother.
We had a plan
in case the worst thing
in the world ever happened.
And it looks like it just did.
Sorry about the mask.
I was just doing a quick exfoliation.
I never have time for self-care.
I always make time.
Is the book safe?
What are you talking about?
Papa never told you about the magic book?
Pardon me, Ken,
but we didn't even know
Papa Smurf had a brother.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you Smurfs don't know
Smurf about Smurf.
With all due respect, Ken, we all Smurf.
In fact, I've probably personally Smurfed
more than you'll ever Smurf.
That sounds like a load of Smurf.
Can you Smurf that Smurf up?
I can Smurf that Smurf up
and have it delivered to your house.
Hey, come on, Smurfs. Stick a Smurf in it.
Smurf that.
- I don't like his Smurfitude.
- Ditto!
Ditto infinity
times infinity plus six. I win.
- Let's just leave it at that.
- Fine!
This is the handiwork
of the evil wizard Razamel.
He plays for keeps.
How do you know that?
The part that he plays
for keeps or the Razamel part?
Well... both?
I know a lot of things, fella.
- Cool. Cool.
- All right.
So let's go find this Razamel and...
And smash him!
I like this guy.
Let's get Papa Smurf back.
"Let's"? You're staying here.
I don't work with amateurs.
Well, joke's on you because
I like being called an amateur.
It means doing something
for the love of it.
And that's me. That's what I do.
Love.
That and a dime'll get you
a phone call in 1986.
What?
Exactly.
You don't get it.
Your enemies are everywhere.
And you have to be ready
to take 'em out like that!
That's one of the most
disturbing world views
I've ever encountered.
Funny coming from a bunch of Smurfs
who don't even know who they really are.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means...
Smurfs are descendants
of mighty guardians.
We swore to protect the four magic books
from the Alliance of Evil Wizards.
But your Papa walked away.
Why would Papa keep that from us?
You'd have to ask him.
I will when we rescue him.
Oh, no, you're not coming with me.
We'd love to come with you!
No! I just said the 100% opposite of that.
Yay, we're going!
So, how do we do this?
Yeah, how do we do this?
Okay.
We do this by storming Razamel's castle,
and we take no prisoners!
Except for Papa.
We'll make sure and grab him.
- Hold down the fort, Moxie.
- Roger that, Captain Ken.
Did you bring the turntable?
The old-timey one?
No, we just went through it.
Come on, guys. The last one through
is supposed to bring the turntable!
How do we make a portal now?
We're not mind readers, ace.
And it doesn't matter,
'cause my friend can
get us there with his magic.
I never heard of a magic Smurf.
My magic confidence
is at a soft "four" right now.
Failure is the best teacher,
No Name. Dare to fail.
Failure would actually be bad.
Papa's counting on us.
Okay, Magic Smurf...
take us to Razamel's castle!
Give it another shot, No Name.
Okay.
Come on, come on.
Take us to Razamel's castle.
Please.
This is good!
Well, I'll be a monkey's uncle
once removed.
You need some serious therapy and a hug.
Well, they're all going to die.
Look. He hates this.
This is so much fun!
Wow.
Can you believe it's been 62 years
since you sent me on my mission
to infiltrate Smurf Village?
Remember?
Yes. Yes, I do.
I just didn't think you'd ever do it.
You're hilarious!
Didn't you get my emails?
No. They must have gone to spam.
Spam? Why would they go to spam?
Fine! I blocked you.
You blocked me? Why?
We can discuss
all of this brotherly business
later during a sidebar. But for now...
Where is the magic book, Papa Smurf?
It's gone. I destroyed it.
You are the worst liar.
I know you didn't. You know why?
- Why?
- Because you're weak!
Like your best friend, Ron.
Don't you talk about Ron!
Look how upset he gets!
Don't worry, I'll get you to talk.
Those other blue rat monkeys
must have taken the magic book with them.
Where are your Smurfs now, Papa?
I'll never tell!
- I have something, sire!
- What is it?
The energy-pulse detector
picked up a fresh portal.
The Smurfs are trying to
infiltrate the castle.
Fortunately, our force field
knocked them off course.
And I know exactly
where it's sending them.
Joel? Let's go.
Wait, you're taking him?
Joel is my favorite hench-minion.
It worked!
It did if you were trying to kill us.
Brace for impact!
I think I just Smurfed my pants.
Hug the walls!
This doesn't feel like Razamel's castle.
That's because it's not.
This is bad.
Oh, no.
Turns out our magic Smurf here
is a bit of a dud.
Maybe you ought to just
stick to clog making.
We've been bounced to
the inter-portal way station
in the Australian Outback.
And now we have to deal
with the Snooterpoots.
Snooterpoots?
They're tricky creatures
who survive out here
by taking advantage
of lost inter-portal travelers.
They like cake.
Here, hold this cake inside
that rock until they bite.
Bite? Why do I have to do it?
- I don't want to lose an arm.
- Don't be a bully, Ken.
I'll do it.
No, no, I got us into this mess.
If anyone needs
to lose an arm, it'll be me.
Hold it out!
No Name!
Keep your hands and feet inside
the vehicle at all times.
- Vehicle?
- And watch your pockets.
Hey! My glasses! I need those!
Cake! Cake! Cake! Cake! Cake!
What's going on? I can't see anything.
Trust me, it's a good thing
you can't see what's coming.
Cake. Cake. Cake. Cake. Cake.
Double double chocolate
with extra chocolate
from Fou de Patisserie, Paris.
That can only mean one thing.
Hello, Kenneth.
Mama Poot.
Am I that predictable?
Well, obviously not or I'd have
known you'd skip town on me.
Come on. We'll always have Paris.
Ooh la la.
Look, Mama, I can explain.
Save it for your bridge club, tough guy.
Words are cheap.
Actions are what matters.
Actions and... cake.
Well... looks like things worked out.
You're doing pretty all right
for yourself.
Yeah, Kenneth, business is booming.
Every yahoo thinks they can
navigate the multiverse these days, so...
Hey, that's permanent!
Looks like you yahoos could use a lift.
Yeah. We really could.
It's an emergency.
It always is.
- It's gonna cost ya.
- We brought cake.
Lots of cake.
You swindling scoundrels!
You don't get to talk
to my Poots like that,
you hear me?
Don't listen to him, my shaggy babies.
The emotionally unavailable Smurf
didn't mean it.
Okay?
Great. Now I'm all out of cake.
Stop it.
You know, I also take cash.
Or a watch.
But Mama Poot, this was a gift
from my grandpa.
Give her the watch, Ken.
Yeah, give her the watch, Ken.
Jeez.
Thank you.
All right, Snooterpoots, it's showtime!
Well, ticktock. Where to? Meter's running.
Razamel's castle.
Oh, no, no, no.
Heck no. No, sir.
Not interested. Deal's off.
What do you mean, the deal's off?
Here.
- This is just the wristband.
- Fine!
Okay, look, h-here's how this goes.
You never saw me,
we never talked, this never happened.
You can't back out now.
Papa Smurf is in trouble.
Guilt doesn't work on me, sister.
Please, Mama Poot, we have to save Papa.
Just drop us off.
No one will ever have to know
you were involved.
The Alliance of Evil Wizards
knows everything.
Nobody, and I mean nobody,
comes back from Razamel's castle alive.
The walls of the moat
are made of the bones
of the ones who tried.
Okay.
We've got a magic Smurf.
Maybe he can stop those wizards.
So you're telling me
your magic is strong enough
to take on the whole evil enchilada?
The whole evil enchilada--
What-what is that?
These wizards have one goal in mind:
To rule the world with evil
by getting rid of all
the goodness in the universe.
And nothing will stand in their way.
So tell me, Magic Smurf,
how you gonna handle that?
I will tell you how.
No Name, come back!
No Name!
No Name, stop!
I can't do it.
I can't take on the whole enchilada.
I don't have it in me, Smurfette.
I know I'm gonna let everyone down.
Hey, don't beat yourself up.
Pressure gets to all of us.
You just have to believe in yourself.
Yeah, but I don't even know
how I'm doing all this magic stuff.
This isn't me.
I can't face off
against a powerful wizard.
Listen.
That voice inside your head
telling you you're not good enough?
That voice is not who you are.
You're the only one
who notices that voice.
Whoa!
Yeah, "whoa."
You just need to decide
who you want to be,
and every day you'll
become yourself a little more.
And before you know it,
that voice will go away.
It worked for me.
I know what's on your mind
I've been there, too
One too many times
It's time to let go
Go live your life
You've got a story
That you got to write
You were born to be great
Born to be real
Born to be wild
You were born to have faith
Faith in yourself
Born to survive
Don't ever let anyone
Say you're not anyone
When the world says Give it up
Keep going
'Cause you're onto something
Don't ever let anyone
Say you're not anyone
So when you feel
Like nothing works
When you try
But it's getting worse
Getting harder By the minute
You don't have To be a cynic
You don't have To have a limit
The universe is telling us
There's something More to life
But you've been only seeing
What's in front of your eyes
You were born to be great
Born to be real
Born to be wild
You were born to have faith
Faith in yourself
Born to survive
Don't ever let anyone
Say you're not anyone
When the world says Give it up
Keep going
'Cause you're onto something
Don't ever let anyone
Say you're not anyone
- You feeling better?
- Yeah.
The part with the kangaroos
was a little weird, though.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
No.
Snooterpoot Village!
Come on.
Mama Poot! What happened?
Razamel took two of my Snooterpoots
and the rest of you Smurfs.
He just took 'em!
He took 'em back to his castle.
Razamel was here?
Yes, he was.
And he just made the biggest mistake
of his miserable little life.
You still want a piece of him?
Oh, yeah.
We'll take the Scream Buggy.
And I'm driving!
The Scream What-y?
Why is it called the Scream Buggy?
Well, she runs on the fuel of your fear.
What? Why?
No idea.
Buckle up!
Hold onto your little Smurf nubs!
- I'm out.
- You can do this.
You! Brick me!
Yeah, yeah!
More fear! More fear!
More fear!
It's raining Smurfs! Hallelujah!
Oh, my sweet Smurfs. Come here.
Papa!
Let me look at you. Are you okay?
We were so worried about you.
Especially me.
I could never forgive myself
if any of you were harmed.
Joel, please hang my travel cape.
Joel, what do you call a group of Smurfs?
A gaggle? A herd? A troop?
A murder?
Let us out of here, Razamel!
Way to give it thirty percent, Papa Smurf.
Great stuff.
Now give me my book.
We told you we don't have it!
And where is my so-called brother?
He's relaxing with his feline associate
in the solarium, sire.
How I hate that cat!
Could we accidentally
help it shed its mortal coil,
Joel, my dear?
As you wish, lord sire.
Joel!
Fetch me a Clamato. Room temp.
Hey, what about us?
Prisoners don't get clam drinks!
But I do have another treat
in store for you.
I hope you like... party games.
We're going to play one called:
Let's Squish A Smurf
Every Time Papa Doesn't Tell Me
Where The Last Magic Book ls...
Till All You Smurfs Are Squashed!
That doesn't sound like a fun game.
Joel, be a doll and move
these fetid degenerate goblins
to the Squishadrome for to squash.
I warned you about getting complacent.
Smurfs, can you give us a minute?
The book is still safe.
But why are my Smurfs here?
It's way too dangerous.
Well, maybe if you hadn't been
hiding away in Smurf Village
for the past 100 years
none of us would be in trouble.
You know I had my reasons for that.
Do you think Ron
would have just walked away?
Who's Ron?
Bringing her in hot!
That cleared out the sinuses.
Hey! You dead?
That was absolutely terrifying.
I think I swallowed my gum.
I'm coming for ya, Poots!
Mama's coming for her babies!
It might be good to not yell so much
and give away our location.
Right, right. Okay.
What is this place?
Munich, autobahn, Razamel's stupid castle.
He thinks it's so spooky.
So how do we get in there?
Well, it's an impenetrable fortress,
so we're gonna have to sneak in.
Okay, let's get some ideas going.
You know, blue-sky time, no judgments.
We pole-vault over the wall.
- That's a terrible idea!
- And that's a judgment.
Maybe we can exploit a weakness
no wizard can resist.
- What kind of weakness?
- A fried weakness.
- Your food is here.
- Who ordered this?
- Razamel Q. Wizard.
- That sounds right.
He complains when his tunic gets too tight
but he's the one
who gets himself in this mess.
So you can just order
any kind of food from anywhere?
Absolutely.
Just make sure you
tip the driver ahead of time
or they'll lick everything.
Okay, here's the plan.
We'll sneak into the castle
inside this bag
and when we get delivered to Razamel,
kablammo! We save everything.
We should have gotten more fries.
I'm a stress eater.
That's good.
It's the quill pen
that my great-great-great
grandfather Zazamel
used to sign the Treaty of the Alliance
of Intergalactic Wizards.
Razamel always worshipped this pen.
I'll just put it behind this.
Enjoying the solarium?
Yes! Very much. Thank you.
You're probably admiring Dadah's urn.
This is Dadah?
Oh, yes! Dadah in all his glory.
Sometimes, when no one's looking,
I sprinkle him into Joel's protein shakes.
You know, Dadah always
wanted us to rule together.
Remember how he said
that was going to happen?
And rule together we shall!
Once we get our hands
on that Jaunty Grimoire,
the whole universe
will be under the darkly magic control
of the Intergalactic Alliance of Wizards.
And finally,
all goodness shall be
eradicated for evermore.
Sounds amazing!
So you'll introduce me
to the Alliance, then?
Of course! Proudly!
But first, what do you schay
we schmoosh some Schmurfs?
I'd say that sounds like music to my ears!
And, hey, I just wanted to say
I'm so glad to be back
and that we're together again.
I love you, Razamel!
Best friend brother friend brother.
Love.
Well, ditto I'm sure.
Come along, Azrael.
We're going to watch
the Smurfs get squashed.
Absolutely repulsive.
We're inside the castle.
Maybe you should slow down on the fries.
You're right. Just one more.
- Are the plates ready?
- Yes, sir.
Hand!
- Ring!
- No ring, Mama.
Where's Terry the food taster?
- I don't know, on break?
- Fine, I'll taste it.
But if I die, I'll kill Terry!
Wait a minute. Did you forget
to order fries again?
You ate all the fries!
I love salty potato-based treats
and I will not apologize for that.
Hey, don't look at me.
I didn't make the order.
Just check again.
What do we do now?
I don't know. Can you magic some up?
Hand incoming!
O magic powers from
up on high, bring us fries.
Bring us fries!
Here they are.
Onion rings! Who ordered this garbage?
They're Razamel's favorite.
- How did you know that?
- No idea. It just came to me.
This way.
Ready, Joel?
Good, it works. First Smurf, please.
Please, Razamel! Don't hurt my Smurfs.
Then tell me where the magic book is.
Somewhere you'll never find it!
Then let's loosen those lips!
Who shall we squash first?
Eenie...
meanie, miney--
I'll go.
Hear that?
That's the clicking sound of evil.
Let's go Smurf that wizard up.
Last chance, Papa!
We're here to save everything!
Deal with my awesomeness.
My, those are dated moves
for such a bold entrance.
State your business, stranger.
Free Papa Smurf at once!
And give me back my babies!
Or what?
Or I shall uncork all of my awesomeness
all over this place!
There must be a cat in here.
Is there a cat in here?
I knew it! Man, the dander gets me.
- Is that what I think it is?
- Uh-oh.
Could it be?
Jaunty Grimoire!
I knew you couldn't hide forever.
I thought you said
the magic book was safe!
How long have you been on my head?
And how did I not feel you there?
I have soft hands. And feet.
And I've only been up there
since you made a wish.
Cha-cha-cha!
I'm magic!
Wait. Were you doing the magic?
Yeah, kind of.
Yeah, but the moonwalking was all you.
Yeah, actually, that was me, too.
I didn't even do the moonwalk?
There's no such thing as a magic Smurf.
Chin up, pal. Don't quit on yourself.
You made a wish for a thing, so...
I just gave you a little head start.
You got a lot more magic in you
than you think.
You just got to let it out.
There's Papa! Hey, Papa!
Thank you for bringing
the final magic book right to me.
Look who it is!
It's our lost little
wizard girl family member.
I'm not part of your family, you freak.
Tut-tut.
Methinks these voluminous
Polaroid photo albums
from your childhood
would tell a different tale.
Here you are when you were clay.
Oh, here you are throwing horseshoes
at a Sunday barbecue.
And look at you laughing
at the caricaturist
who drew you in front of the Eiffel Tower.
That's me?
You may have looked different,
but you were always one of us.
Why don't I remember any of this?
And here you are enjoying
the wizard's favorite snack...
French fries. How you loved your fries!
That's a lie! I hate fries!
I knew I didn't like her for a reason.
She's the darn enemy!
No, I'm a Smurf!
And P.S., newsflash, and FYl,
that's not who I am now.
You can never change what you really are.
Don't listen to him, Smurfette!
You're with us, now and always.
That's right! I'm with him. And them.
You sure about that?
You did exactly what
you were created to do.
You brought me Papa Smurf and Jaunty.
The final piece of the evil puzzle.
Ergo ipso delicto... I win.
Time to rule the universe.
I want to stay with Papa. Papa!
Jaunty Grimoire!
What a wonderful moment.
Too bad it has to be
interrupted by... reality!
- No!
- Chiballog badoo!
Bomba gee joo--
Wait a minute. What am I reading?
Yes, that's better.
May dark power course through
your pages now and forever!
I don't want to be evil!
I... am... Grimoire.
- No!
- Yes.
Well, thanks for saving me
a lot of squish time. See ya!
Wait. I'm not going with you?
To meet with the other wizards?
That's a big fat no!
This is the end of the road
for you, Gargamel.
But you said "Ditto"
when I said I loved you.
- I lied.
- I'm telling Mother!
Mother never respected you...
or your stupid cat.
Goodbye, Smurfs, and so long, brother...
forever!
I'm so sorry, everyone.
I'm sorry, too.
This is my first job
out of college, though.
I need a good review on my Linkedln.
Well, you're not getting one from me.
Fair enough.
That's pretty impressive engineering.
I can't believe I'm the one
who's gonna get smashed.
At least I'll be thin.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
I love you.
What? What are you doing?
It doesn't go down like this.
Yes, I may loathe the Smurfs
with the fury of a thousand burning suns
but I loathe my brother more
for disrespecting me
and my sweet, sweet Azrael.
And I've had enough of
said respectlessness.
Run, Smurfs! Run!
Prisoner escape! Prisoner escape!
Good idea, Azrael. Engage wing spell!
Look at me. I'm going to
need a bigger litter box.
Oh, my.
- Bring it!
- Come on, Ken!
I don't run from a fight.
We're not leaving you, brother.
All Smurfs and Snooterpoots spoken for.
Excelsior, my sweet Azrael!
I'm not feeling so majestic.
Assume crash positions!
Happy Birthday--
This is all my fault.
I can't believe I did
exactly what that wizard wanted me to do.
I'm so sorry, No Name.
No. This is my fault.
The only reason any of this happened
is because I wanted to find my thing.
If I hadn't been so selfish,
none of us would be here.
No. It's not your fault, No Name.
And it certainly isn't yours, Smurfette.
This is all my fault.
I kept secrets from you all.
And that was wrong.
I didn't want to lose any of you
the way we lost Ron.
Who's Ron?
He was the greatest Smurf who ever lived.
I should have told you
about him a long time ago.
You're safe with us, little one.
- I've got her, Ron.
- Those evil wizards won't get you.
Ron!
He was a Smurf of
tremendous courage and valor...
and really, really great hair.
It's good to see you, my brothers.
It's been too long.
We just had Smurfberry juice
and waffles together.
Like I said, it's been too long.
That magic book will be mine!
Well, that was a bit of a letdown.
Now that's more like it!
He dispatched baddies with a Smurfy blend
of elegance and lethality.
I think it was safe to say
that Ron loved everyone and everything
no matter how small
or insignificant they may seem.
I love you, brother. Or sister.
He was way ahead of his time.
But Razamel soon got the upper hand.
That's really something else.
I should probably start with
this one next time.
Baby Jaunty!
No!
- Hang on! Papa's coming!
- I got you!
Save the book!
You're next!
More vortex.
Grab my hand, Ron!
I probably should have cut my hair,
like you guys suggested.
You always were a free spirit.
It was an honor and privilege
guardianeering with both of you.
No!
Fi-i-i-i-ist buu-u-u-u-mp!
Ron... was gone.
Now, I won't ask you again.
- Give me that baby book.
- No.
- No?
- Hey.
No! Not in the face!
That's why I created Smurf Village.
So I could keep all of you safe.
I couldn't lose any of you
like we lost Ron.
There isn't a day goes by
that I don't think about him.
I know, brother.
It's time I told you
about our higher calling.
We Smurfs are Guardianeers of Good.
- What does that mean?
- It means...
that we have always been protectors
of peace and harmony in the universe.
Even Smurfs who don't have a thing?
Yes, No Name.
But it's not just some thing
you call yourself.
And it isn't who you are.
It's who we are.
It's the sum of all its parts.
It's brains and brawn.
It's a Smurf who always fights
for what she believes in.
And even a Smurf who thought
he didn't have any thing
but is willing to give everything.
I'm not gonna sugarcoat this, Smurfs.
The bad guys want to destroy
everything good in the world.
And they can do it.
But we're not gonna let them!
Because there is nothing
we can't accomplish
if we do it together!
Now let's get that book
and save the universe!
Let's do it for Ron!
Let's get to Guardianeering!
Wait! Where are we going?
- Way to kill the mood, Glasses.
- He's right.
Razamel and that book could
be anywhere in the universe.
Attention!
Attenzione!
I know exactly where
the wizards have taken all four books.
Now, I will share this information
with you vicious garden weasels
on one condition.
- Name it.
- That I be in the room
to see the stupid, angry look
on my stupid, angry brother's
mean, stupid, angry face
when he sees you all alive and thriving.
It's a spite mission.
I think we got it.
We all get what we want.
But after that,
our little alliance is over.
Yeah, okay, deal. Where to, freaky-deaky?
To the ninth dimension,
the nexus of space and time
that represents
all possible worlds and all--
- Just get in the car!
- Yes. Sorry. Of course.
Yeah!
Hello, everyone! I have big news.
And it involves me and my magic book.
What a surprise. Raz-a-mope is late.
What could you have been doing?
Having your hair cut by a blind raccoon?
Do you know what?
I'm sick of being treated
like garbage by all of you,
with your sarcastic comments
and mock merriment.
Late and lame.
You're all lame!
You'll make wonderful hench-minions
now that I'm the lord of the universe.
Solo! Me. I. Moi!
Well, time to start chanting.
Yeah-- no chance I'll hit that note.
And here we go!
Ommm beklartz...
flunknard!
You have got to be kidding me.
The Guardianeers of Good are here.
We'll try not to hurt you,
but we're not making any promises.
It's not bragging.
That's just me being real.
This is bad.
He's linked all the books.
Ken, we need a plan.
We're Guardianeers, Papa. We are the plan.
- Charge!
Hold on!
Well, that's adorable.
Kachow!
Your goodness is mine!
Into the vortex, Smurf spirits.
Razamel stole their Smurfy goodness.
We can get them back
if we break the spell by rescuing Jaunty.
Where are you going, traitor?
Traitor?
Well, I brought the Smurfs to you!
This was a spite mission.
It was.
- In the water bottle you go.
- No!
He's distracted.
You thought I forgot about you?
Whose goodness shall I take first?
No!
Papa!
Don't give up, my precious Smurfs.
You're Guardianeers.
It's up to you now.
Smurfette?
My work is done.
I finally delivered everything you wanted,
Your Evil Lordship.
What is this?
I have always been on your side.
What? No!
Well, well, well.
That's what we in the evil business
call the long con.
Welcome home, sinister Smurf demon.
Thank you.
Psych!
Got you, Jaunty!
Thank you, Smurf--
Stop! That's the interdimensional abyss.
Anyone who goes in there never
ever comes back the same.
You've got nowhere to go.
What do we do now, Jaunty?
Warning! Lose the heels.
You're really not gonna like
this first dimension, Smurfette.
Why?
Clay?
That's why I feel
overly thick and bloated.
Where's the book?
Give that back to me!
That's what happens to handsy fellas.
- Find a door!
- Go, Smurfette!
This is the worst dimension!
Stay away from erasers!
- What's that?
- What?
- Made you look.
- Come on.
Help! Help! A mean old wizard got me!
Eraser!
That's my book, you freakish popinjays!
Oh, no! I can only run from left to right!
Here! Jump up these tiny hills.
This dimension isn't so hard, actually.
Hand over the eight-bit book, Smurfs,
or face the wrath of my evil picket fence!
It'll take more than a fence to stop us.
You!
Now you shall taste the Might!
With Smurf filled anguish!
Ugh! This is my least favorite dimension.
What are you?
I'm a tardigrade,
the most rugged micro animal
in the universe.
Our motto is "Live tiny, die never."
Hi, Tardi, nice to meet you, bye!
Nice to meet you, too! Bye!
I just want a friend.
Will you stay here with me forever?
Absotively not!
Is this...
Smurf Village.
We're home.
Cha-cha-cha!
All you have to do
is get me to Papa Smurf's mushroom house
and I can hide away for
another hundred years, easy!
Welcome back.
Papa.
You're okay.
I've never been better.
It's good to have you home.
We did it, Papa.
Keep her safe.
I knew you'd come through...
Smurfette.
I don't understand.
Let me explain.
We're in the surreal dimension.
It's made of your dreams and nightmares.
No.
Thank you for your service.
Time to rid the universe
of all things good.
Bye-bye, puppies.
Ciao, daisies.
He's done it.
He's sucking all of the goodness
out of the universe.
What the shell?
Release Jaunty!
We're not gonna let this happen, Razamel.
And just who is going to stop me?
You?
You are nothing!
I'm not nothing.
Then who are you?
I'm... I'm...
That's what I thought.
You're nobody.
No Name!
Can you hear me?
Who are you, No Name?
Who are you?
Yeah, who?
I... I-I don't know.
You should've just stuck to clog making.
Stay with me, No Name.
Please.
You got more magic in you than you think.
That voice inside your head
telling you you're not good enough?
That voice is not who you are.
I don't know who I am, Papa.
And I don't think I ever will.
I know who you are.
You're kind and fair.
You're strong because you're determined.
You remind me a lot of Ron in that way.
Really? How?
He was resilient.
When Ron got knocked down,
he'd get right back up on his feet.
Just like you.
But Ron knew who he was. He had a thing.
Not at first.
Some Smurfs just take a little
more time to find their thing.
And, No Name... it's your time.
La... la... la-la-la-la...
What? What are you saying?
La, la, la-la-la-la...
I know who I am.
Hey! We're not done!
I've had just about enough of you!
No Name!
But-But how?
Who are you?
Call me
I'm-The-Smurf-Who's-Gonna-
Kick-Your-Big-Giant-Butt Smurf!
The Smurf-Who's-Gonna-Kick-
Your-Big-Giant-Butt Smurf?
I don't know, I think it's got
a bit of pizzazz.
You don't like it, do you?
I don't care what you call yourself!
One lone Smurf can't take on
the whole evil enchilada!
That's the difference
between you and me, Razamel.
I'm not alone.
La, la, la-la-la-la
La, la, la-la-la
Smurfette...
La, la, la-la-la-la
La, la, la-la-la
Sing a happy song
La, la, la-la-la-la...
Why are you singing that dreadful song?
Because we are the Guardianeers of Good.
And I believe you have something of ours.
Wow.
No!
No, stop it! Stop this right now!
Amazing.
What?
No!
Wait.
What are you doing?
Smurfette, I command you
to help me at once!
You're an evil wizard and always will be!
Not true. Who I am is up to me.
I decide.
I am a Smurf.
We may be small, we may be adorable,
but don't mistake
our kindness for weakness.
Because kindness always wins.
Unite in Smurfitude!
No! My books!
They're not evil anymore!
Cha-cha-cha!
That's good.
Hey, everybody.
I hate you.
I know.
Thank you, No Name.
I mean... what did you
call yourself again?
I'm-The-Smurf-Who's-Gonna-Kick-
Your-Big-Giant-Butt Smurf.
You're right. Terrible.
I can beat that.
Wait!
What about Kick ♪♪♪♪ Smurf?
Kick ♪♪♪♪ Smurf is definitely
inappropriate.
You're lucky Sound Effect Smurf is here.
Sorry. I don't know what the ♪♪♪♪
I was thinking.
Hey! I said "Smurf."
You know, maybe
I'll stick with Magic Smurf.
It-It's got a nicer ring to it.
It's classic.
Kid... you earned your name.
Give it up for Magic Smurf!
- Magic Smurf!
- That makes so much sense.
How did this happen?
You came up against
the Guardianeers of Good.
This is for Ron.
- You missed me, idiot.
- Did I?
No! No!
Help me, dear brother!
I... I...
love you.
Funny how you're finally
able to say it now.
How about Azrael?
How do you feel about
my precious feline associate?
He has feelings, you know.
I love you, Azrael.
In the immortal words of
Azrael's favorite pop crooner
and social provocateur, Jonathan Mathis,
"too much, too little, too late."
No! No!
You will all pay!
Well, that was quite
the successful spite mission.
I'm off.
It's Razamel!
Did somebody say... Ron?
It's Ron!
Judging by the smile
on everyone's face, looks like
the Guardianeers of Good
took care of business.
These Smurfs were more
than up to the task.
And they did it their own way.
Ron! I thought you were a goner!
Well, if by goner, you mean I was stuck
in the tenth dimension
guarded by every variation
of vicious dragon
in every possible variation
of the universe
then you'd be right. I was a goner.
So, what did I miss in the last 106 years?
Well, that depends.
Are you thinking about time
in a linear fashion
or as a series of flat circles?
What?
Exactly.
What do you say we get out of here
and head back home,
where life is good and things
don't crunch our brain so much.
That sounds pretty Smurfy to me.
My dear Smurfs,
we will no longer hide away
from the world.
Whenever we're called to action,
we'll be there.
Because we're stronger together!
Best friends forever and ever...
Help me!
Joel! Joel!
Break time's over, Joel.
We have unfinished business
with those Smurfs.
English (US)