Welcome aboard for now, fashion your life
Belts, we're taking off to big wing
four
Abe, seven urs
af trust
This film is based on real life events
The Apostle is an imaginary Ridhi. This movie is a
It is not a scholarly film i.e. a documentary and
It is based on historical facts or actual
not considered a realistic depiction of events
Should. some characters,
This film is aimed at any person,
Organizations, religion, caste groups, caste,
communities, institutions, professions or nationalities
To defame the feelings of, to hurt,
Not to insult or hurt. movie
Producer and associated with the film
And under the copyright laws of the world
Is protected. film or any of its
unauthorized display, distribution,
Copying, stealing or copying Citizen
Gives rise to criminal prosecution. this
Producer of the film
I have tried everything but PM
ISI is involved in international media
It has been reported that our negotiations
has completely failed and at any time
The terrorists will give a bar to the professional soldiers sitting above.
Sir tell me this is not true
is
Sir, just give me your promise.
Yo we will have to become even one telest
And all our passengers from here
Will be able to take this bus safely
The last three Costinger family members
For the last few days, it has been PM Dewas.
religion
Zahoor will not be saved on Baddog's boat.
what
Have you decided?
Talks have been held with the PM. Tomorrow all three,
Mushtaq Ahmed Zardar, Ahmed Omar Sahid Shaikh
And your brother Mulana Masood Azar.
The darkness here after breaking away from our prisons
will be handed over to you in
Ten million dollars to Azrab
transferred to dubai contact
will go
now
I would like to talk to the passenger in private
am
All of you read your own books.
can take off and open the windows
be nervous
I am Ajay Sanyal Bharte, IB Chief, you
want to give good news
I am sure that our negotiation was successful.
All of you leave safely for India.
will be this
to maintain courage in difficult circumstances
Our country is forever grateful to you for this
India will remain female
Who is the most coward among them?
Intelligent sir, we should come to Baita tonight.
called the golden bird
This was your country, wasn't it? Today gold was also looted,
Tomorrow the bird will also fly away.
Ganiyal Saheb, we live in the neighborhood
Use as much force as you can and spoil it.
can spoil
all
Don't feel bad that we are apart from you
Negotiating team with these experienced people
Had it happened if our command doors on that plane
Even if India were to be stormed,
There would be a better strategy for reputation.
So according to you, your reputation
To save the lives of 160 innocent people
Putting on is a better strategy I have
handled this kind of situation before
let's be frank our country is not
to handle this kind of adversity so then
we better start preparing so that it is done
All even all one asked for us to bite
On our diplomatic routes he
Diya Sir I'm sorry I'm being rather blunt
but I have no choice from Kashmir
Now do something on your hand from work
will go and all of us sitting here from wherever
Sir, I am going to make a good Kun.
To break my mind
So that even if it is against India,
Don't even think about it, we are sitting in his bed and looking at him.
need and for this I have a unique
The whole plan is silent Sanyal, that's you
The whole country is a scoundrel of my plan.
Have you seen that it happens?
What about Madam Mathai?
My address has been registered, SBI
In security. Bang le sir ma'am. you too
That's what I told you, sir.
Madam. Thank you. When did you get the job? It got installed today itself.
I've got a problem.
all, all, all, oh
There have been some playdates inside or
Thankful for the Parliament session outside.
jargon 40 minis back kids some mps that
Let's bang on the Parliament core inside
Traction has been run i setvent 4k
Sunny one of the hitchhikes
Pullman attacks have shaken a lot
No one had even thought that the government would
Peem is very worried
Has the darkness ever broken?
Sometimes breaking the wall is good for the country.
The file you gave can be proved.
eyes car
If it takes a lot to make friends with the Middle East
It will take time and Pakistan will suffer financially
going bankrupt is just too bushkin
Because they have US backing yes
There is a suggestion which the PM liked
if
PM was concerned that such a long term plan
Will be successful we have no choice
It's better to talk badly than ever before
Because from today onwards sir is busy in the house, tomorrow is the wedding.
Will sit down too and then have something to break
There will be no patience or courage left.
will make it happen
which
so turandar
I am not one of these.
No, no, go away friend, come after this.
How much do you load?
It looks glossy
This is petrol.
Pakai, Colban, Colban, Colban,
Colban
Has it happened?
i doubt
What is Naan?
Amdal Amdal Amdal Amdal
Son, what's your name?
Mataliye in Hamzar.
Keep losing, keep losing, like this.
Yes, guma, guma, guma, guma. Come, that
Leases apply. Will be defeated.
Will pick it up, add Pithani Godhri also.
It was fine then.
Always keep the edge of both sharp. yours
purpose
There is nothing in front of Satpa. whole change
But to rule.
Probably this is the first place Liari comes to.
Where I worked for six years
I have slept on Glass Gohe for six years
to create a network
your
I want immortal company, I add salt from here
I like that people feel weird
A
So tea was also made salty. tea here
Reminds me of my home.
Where is your house?
scale
It will not be easy for Gusta to join the gang of thieves.
Might have to wait. Labma
So and so. All the gangs there are in Lyari.
All because of whom?
So it is strong. That's why only Rehman Balwati
K gang can't get up. children from pathan gang
Babu Dakhet and Ashrat Bappu's people Khomte
Live. Like that night.
Rehman Dakhet, Babu
Dakhet. Dakhet appears in the name of both.
Liari K
The day Rehman came to know about this, he
It is said that his mother has become impure.
Rahman murdered his mother in public
did it
Why you idiot?
Come on, open it and take out the goods, come on! Rehman's salwar
Entering and taking a big staff?
That Bavo Bhai, Ravan Bhai took care of his child.
When asked to set up a stall in Bati Fati, I felt like
Further. Come on, open it and take out the goods, come on!
let's go and open the goods
Where did you get this greasy litchi?
After this he decided to fight Rehman Baloj
Has joined hands with Arshat Pappu for this.
Today's date is approximately one Chiayi Lihari
But the occupation of Arshat Pappu and Babu Dakhayat
Is. Rahman himself will not come to tomorrow's wedding.
on
not his son
Rizwan, Hamza, Thamza, Rizwan, Ise
Kesma was fresh,
As soon as you arrive, join the ranks of Arshat Pappu.
Has gone.
pill
Life can be lost in this work only from there.
There may be danger of, will run, or someone else
Use a trick?
i'm saving the boy
So go ahead, look orange, not orange.
this
no
This Raman cannot lift the force. RJD.
At Tekan. not you but your blind
Come. Till this gives support.
do it
do it do it
do
He is dead, get out of here and press his chest.
chest compressions, hey
The bat has been shot, hey the bat has been shot
It's on, hey, is there a doctor or an ambulance?
Bring it, bring the ambulance, scratch the hoof, no
Mia, hey get a car
Brother, someone
my son's
blood
is
Ramata works in my shop Laiti
Poor guy has given his entire life to Japa.
Di in saving the child
one
one one one one one one one one one one one one one
one one one one one one
one
Do you know a lot about insects?
Yes.
Where I come from it's normal. from where
Is it?
Kharutabad, Ketta. Do you know how to use a gun?
Yes. How?
Elder brother joined me in Azad Baloch Army
Were. He is the one who has said everything. now said
Is it?
Martyred. Is there any other restal?
no sir
We are fake tombs. Longe, yes brother. it
Give it a try. So save the fencer's life.
I don't want money. What?
what did you say?
I don't want money Mia.
Whatever I could do in exchange for this
That's what I tried to do.
a goodbye friend
my love
Is.
Because, child you
Mine. Don't do any bullying. state
Election is in heaven. that's some revenge
Take. PAP is sitting next to Rahman.
Yadar, stom what happened in an election.
He was dramatized, Dar FT Choujari
Astram took it away, I was the one
Milto had taken Likal in Celtro,
But still how much will be affected by the election results?
The dirty officer had increased, should he go here or not?
Once the elections are over
Keep an eye on your brother don't leave him alone
I swear to you that you are my dead mother.
You will see me die, I swear you will see me die
eat ok well done my time star baby
let's go unchallenged
Our love will not come back to us now.
Shabeel has to think about Mustaquil
attack what explained what is doing
Friend, you are standing stitched, are you not injured at the top?
P A P has more control over W A in his work.
For Pepi we asked our couple twice locally.
The election is on its own and is on the other side.
Mushli Movement Patting, MMP Joe Babu
What if Rakshat is a supporter of Pappu?
It's a simple thing that captured the whole imagination
Didn't he?
Bharra Adam would have made a better lattice than a nail.
We are here. the most in entire Pakistan
We are in the business of fake guns here
Pay. Taxes were equalized. There is no difference between good and fake
Can't tell much difference. yes a little hot
it gets done quickly
Thirsty murders etc. lakhs of diaries
People's life is going on because of us
All looks work well with these boys
So the next task would have already been done.
I will make you understand, stay son, stay son
keep up the good work and see this also
here
that's not what you're seeing
It is hard to get what Reman Bhai did.
Who knows how many?
on which holes are made
In Basle we have schools for Liari, Ballejas,
hospitals get everything built
Are.
Come over. Come over.
So this is the room, Udar Kitchen, here first Rahman
Brother's son-in-law
Used to do. This is Liari, complete from here
Liari looks on. Yes Lodu, come on!
shows umbrella
Today this women's society stands in Nawababad.
Ragivara Shabeg
Lane Singu Lane these are some areas Arshat
These people are in the hands of Papko and Babude Pais.
Looking at Takki from there Agra Taj Colony
Alma Eqbal Colony Baghdadi Bihar
k
This Babu and Pappugi yes yes that black code
If you go, keep in mind that S.P. Aslam said
This S.P had picked up Reman Bhai from here.
Who is Aslam?
Many years, sisters, one devil and one jinn.
now radha sex happened 9
The one who will be born after Pisces will be named Pari.
Now its purpose is, we are special, no one
If we both need it, that's it!
What are you doing, what are you doing, I can see
I have been there, you are yours, now yours
am,
The entire Liari knows that the attacker is Mashoor Pathan.
Gang leader Babu Daket was from the districts of
But no arrests were made anywhere.
There is no news, the surprising thing is that
Rahman also did not retaliate then
Have done that the upcoming election
To know the rest of the news about garage, visit our
Stay connected together.
He ate well today. eh meretona sail like this
Gave. Will give.
Yes. Give it. I don't eat. hey so yellow
why stay alive
Will do. Yellow. were were were. Hamza.
are you ok?
Football taught me not to do it here.
right now
I was not here to ask for it
pretend divine
Should one take revenge for no?
I should slap a brother out of fear of you.
he is speaking the truth brother
Revenge must be taken but not now
That Babu is waiting for help after the election.
that we will retaliate and if we do anything
If I do, my sons will die.
yes yes
The amount of money they get for running the gang
Yes, everything will stop brother.
you,
What would you have done if you were in my place?
Will take revenge. Mom, did your touch spoil it?
Kiss.
Bao.
You are a robber of forces, child.
The enemy brutally killed your son.
Gave. If the child does not take revenge, then
Peshti belonged to the entire community
Is. And if you want to win the election
If you are not taking revenge, then when will you hold elections?
You have to capture the entire Liari.
Babu at this time
attacked because he is sure that the election
Due to PAP you never get counter attack
Will let you do it. The reality is that it is absolutely
The mat will not be ready.
This is his full opportunity.
Liari's awaam has been abandoned by whom in Karachi?
There will be rule and now in Liari
Hukumat Shere Baroji Hoga
Brother, how much did you make today? brother how much today
made?
Then brother, you are the Nirbani of Allah.
hurry up
I
along the street
Well listen to this in Agyanabad Kala Kate
Cylinder blast has become as big as Liari's.
There is also a police force, I want it here and
If the roads and streets for 40 minutes
want empty
Imran Khan or Imran Khan, Kamana Captain
Imran
to fall on things
no one will come in between
do
Baloch will rule in Sylviyari today
whatever
This will be the hope for someone who will betray.
Never before in history has such a victory been achieved.
Was not seen. win by chili snake moto
Mr. Zamani Jamali believes that
Karashi is just the beginning, Marty Fejerin and
District resident Muhtarma Benazir Bhutto Sahiba
on return from london
Pur
That you can change my wife.
do it do it do it
do it do it
do it do it do it do it
two
Jamid Jab calls you on stage for photo
I am only you
Javid Bhai, Aslamulekum, how are you then?
Assalamulekum, Assalamulekum,
Aslamulekum,
Jarwari has full support for the party he is with.
That if you are with me then this time's national
Elections also won, Inshallah
We can help each other a lot today
Viyari is very keen on our business
chew you
more investors there
Do you know that the sun does not stand still, Babu Dhakyat
But I had got you ready for me now.
Now I don't do good
good good good
good
Nadle these Saptims, I my own party
Take this and step into politics. what
is your trick?
Have you gone to Kabara?
Hey, I will be the leader of your party. but
With a different batchhan,
So that the boat of Muslim Mudda Pati can be cut down
Can give you.
My child is giving away the distance.
What are you talking about?
I am coming, what is it?
you need to talk to your mother
Don't you have any taste? What about main? this method
To do? This Tammeez? This is the link to every curse.
Is the phone here or this phone when you wake up in it
So whose phone did you hit? It looks very red.
not red but bereft
Those Lagdu are not hapless, are they?
both Khanani brothers
How much do you pay per month brother?
Strictly speaking, Forex
I care about the business as much as I can.
Would have earned around three crore rupees in fake Sam.
What happened was heard that Hali
In Hindustani 500 and 1000 rupees
If you have received a blat for cursing a note, then this is
For these people, maybe I have a mother.
Business above Rs 50 to 7 crores
will do
From Karachi to Qatar via sea and then from Qatar
Plane cargo in nepal in nepal
There is some airport minister whose son is this
All goods cross the border to Uttar Pradesh
Now he is fattened in the slaughterhouse of
All work in the grocery stores is done in cash.
yes
Tell me brother, I was thinking about joining politics.
If you want to do big Karanama, then use such wealth.
You must maintain friendship.
The moon can reach only as far as Lyari
If you want to reach then burn yourself among the rich
will have to be scattered
Tuniya Di Sun Dina Bahri Jawaani Masti
Chamstai Poisonous Youth
nights
To avoid the love of 'I have danced on your dance'
Burger children's party is going on
Kasum's raid is on you, you will get lakhs of rupees for the dead body.
will fuck
I have given you this wish today.
Beat Vance Live
Sorry, looks like we've run out of oil.
I leave this home first.
No, no, I am talking about my house, I am leaving.
Jangi, thank you. Yes it is so, my
Mother used to say, to protect women
The person gets the opportunity.
You make them dance my Jandat's chair. Or
Courage.
Hammat. You were in the rally this day, you too
In politics with Abbo
Are. The truth will probably be very bitter for you and
Today I don't have the courage to speak Jut.
If you have the courage, come today.
My full name is Hamza Ali Mazari. i
Rahman joins Maloj's gang
Am. His stars are with him in the dark blessed ones
I give.
But I am also fond of Shaadi. Mir, Faiz,
Iqbal, Ghalim.
Doesn't smoke, doesn't drink alcohol. one today
cigars
your trust was left with me
we did Karaj
mafia network so
Strong enough to penetrate them
It is getting difficult, we have killed the mafia.
UP mafia pilfered from us
Network is not filtering
The political backing of these terminals is so much
Is it strong enough to arrest them?
Bring it and somehow find and arrest Sabu.
Even if taken, the communal rights are their backup.
Within two hours their people covered entire UP
Will give We need a government which
That Arbandh should find out why I
why do people help
that the biggest enemy of Indians
is Indian
that Pakistan is proud of its enemy
come
Major Iqbal's Aap Bas Darwari Kaal Meets
Have been a traveler. Come Rahman Bhai, come.
This is Sajit Neer from Lashkar. this abdoor
Batavi Aajan Sheema. Yes.
Know. And the biggest of all the projects
Run training cam. good
trainee
Taj Paisha is on Niyari. such a
It is too late to crown a political person.
then again
So I promise that if Niari's
Action will be your victory. And you are beige and
Iqbal came brother. Teman Bhai. of their choice
market of Pakistani politics
It is only by their grace that we can do such a big business.
Be able to do. Brother Javij, God would have mercy.
Is. We follow orders as per our choice.
Are doing. Come, let's start talking about work.
Sit down.
mercy
Brother.
Asala Baruch to you in large numbers
Should.
But not dirty, absolutely pure.
Guns that bear the name of Russian Americans
Be pierced, our name.
If there is an international investigation tomorrow
If you go, the name of Christian should not come.
Our palos united forces and their no
The Caliphs have blessed you
He who has been bestowed with the title is your Messiah.
I appreciate what you say
will never be able to deny this
You buy all the goods from them at our price
Will give a lot
Baloj is fighting the Lihami of Azad Mulk
Why would they give us their guns?
Major will not give up on company at all.
ISI and Rangers in
has killed many BUF fighters
In the name of interrogation, 70 of his relatives
so got him killed
But Rahwan Bhai is in Pakistani politics today
Whoever has ruled till now has done everything
They reached their destination only by doing some wrong things.
If you like in this hammam
If you want to get down, you will have to be naked.
For the first of the next month 3 October 10
-12 Mujaid wants to go to India this time for a while
They have a bigger purpose than their stalled car.
If there is juul then all the goods till night before.
Riman Bhai should reach us from
don't worry
Not only financially but I myself
Yours sincerely, Sarwari Saab.
I can promise that where
Jarwari Saheb could never avoid it.
okay
It is also. All this material will be given to you in the next
Inshallah we will reach till Dumja. Prakam
Done in dollars. i promised you
Gone.
You know, don't talk about old people.
will be
Rehman Lagaid's accidental death
the big butcher swears
Yes, tell me Javid. Had come. Liari Chinna
Wants you. If Reman
If you spread it on yourself then your chair too
Will go and forget it. Is?
If you want to kill the devil, then kill the devil.
Will have to.
Looks like it's time to free Jin
Where is Mufti?
I have gone on Haj, the great Lord has sent me.
What not?
Where are you from?
Of daily.
Oh wow!
Baruchistan? Aah. And these two?
Hey then you come out my brother.
I serve you a nice drink
Come in yoga form, keep coming, yes now this point
of
to run away to the point
This big sir is a pussy. What do you think?
Mufid, this sahib together with the big sahib's goods
You will crush the rain from it, and tap it
Will pick it up and leave.
cocaine has no fragrance
Webs, mahi this and that tail in a packet of pyre
Who installs the compressor?
fire
so maybe it's gone a long way
police
I had a very young partner in the days of
Aseez was great brother, all love is great
I used to do it and then he started finding me that
My future wife will be beaten by me.
what happened next
In one operation the barrel of the gun was turned towards him
Yes, take out your hands
Instead, it was hung on the fiance's doorstep.
I always say big
Clean, but can rely on fun,
But not on palos.
Go on Jamit, just saw three towers, one more
I had a desire to see, this
Your call has come, tell me what can you do?
are? Hey you, leave me, tell me where did you come?
Come,
This is jealousy Reman Bhai
That you should respect yourself that they
You are shaking hands with these
With the board against which our brothers fight every day
The fight for freedom is going to be fought every day
Children are being killed and respect is being robbed.
Who is ready to finish us?
Sir, don't show me this community's trauma.
I have eaten my own lap
The community ate the child for the sake of the community, my community
Now I have taken it back a bit
So why don't you guys snatch your love away from you?
Mother Azat will chase me
3 October Bara Mujha Hai Wala from Karachi
of
Neither the board nor the aerial charge
Can catch.
I feel it too. board
Must be learning. Gujarat. gujarat target
Will happen.
Message has come on Bittur Forest. you also came
Is. Same Same Thrice in the Morning Third Off in the Morning
Message regarding Karachi port has come. tango
Has also come from nine but its location is poor
Said to be a monkey. same ten to twelve heavily
Common Taylorist.
p
Do this, Naval Intelligence and
Inform Gujarat ATS. They'll
it from there.
to Ajay
Ajay
to
Jib le wahit karna ke like and ya tak sayar
Baavi ke like ke like ke like ke like ke
like
As long as we keep ours, we take it as our own.
Take it till you keep it. Agul take it till you keep it.
are
Have to keep it in Doon. Rani Saheb, Shebaz and So
Baluk Bandu's
Arrangements were made for medical coaching
Mirrors. And that too in Karachi. stay, eat
It is our responsibility. you just had supper
The date has to be decided. we'll take care of the rest
Have been.
Nana has a lot of expectations from you son.
It's your blood, isn't it Baloch?
Try doing this a little for the sake of freedom.
What happened to you Balochistan?
If you can get freedom then yes I will take command
Aji Shiraz sir, this is from our side
it's a small sight
If before the Jumeirah of the next minute - before
Once it is complete, it
will go
to Ajay
Ajay
to
Arshat Pappu is still fine. Rehman
Dagayat is being over-hyped. 1997
There was a chance to encounter him. that day you
He had saved him. is your relative
No. So many tricks for your politics
You him. I heard that Larry's election
I want to stand in family and politics as one.
Aslam Mihan does not come into the jungle.
No one has disrespect, hey hey his mother
Can he caress anyone?
How many years has passed since your suspension?
together with year
That's why I say that we have lied together over the years.
How did this situation happen in this country?
The one who doesn't appreciate his true skills is suspended
you also made me
I can't, I can't live.
True, after such a long time, you don't need such a friend.
no
is
If you did it in the excitement of youth, then a
you made a mistake
The important thing is that now I
I want to make it completely clear, right?
Galdagi na ugar goonda and do this noble work
will be the first step there
yours
Repost
To use it properly. It is melting, isn't it? this
Your rezoning letter. go wake up fumal
My liar. you are mine
Well son, what's the matter? Yela. Chuk. Good
It seemed that you came back to me dumb.
But I will not do this work
The mess you're asking me to clean up
No, I won't be able to do this alone, Liari.
A policeman guards Rehman Deket.
I will be tortured before the first encounter.
The crowd must have left from there, then the solution
what is it my brother
Liari
toss
Don't ever try to bribe my boys
If you don't need it, there is a secret office of your grandson.
about which outsiders will never know
One more important thing I don't know
There is no mischief in my ways
you won't do it either
only then i
ltd
Let's go and add twelve methods on time.
Lee, nak nak time is mine.
Are you going to college or going to college?
I am going to coaching, now I want some money.
Were.
Why?
Today is the third way, coaching fees will increase.
Is. But mother said...
Or should I make some arrangements?
I will give you the spoon of Kuma's hand.
All the arrangements were made by you in Moong.
I will definitely go to my mother. It seems that she has gone to her mother.
I grow on such trees?
We do so much of mine every now and then
If you are mine, these winds are yours, if you are mine
all the ways
If you are mine, I am yours.
If you, this light of mine is yours
If you surrender my heart to you, if you are mine
i
I am yours
u metical is an excuse
I want to get out of some house Tato
If I have a day left, Papa, why don't you buy some burgers, kid?
Will you marry me to a burger kid?
Otherwise who else will I marry?
Come come, Heed Mubarak. Come, Heed Mubarak.
Come from him, Heed Mubarak Come from him, Heed
happy
from him
Oh dear Mia, you have failed again in the end.
Gone, looks like you also want to become a miniature, my
You have become twelve sons, what can you say brother?
I feel jealous in your love, and I want to stay away from you.
even walking
Yes, I also have to change some of my colors, I
Give me Haliya...
if my salt
If my path is yours then my land will be destroyed.
This man will bet inside
man
So this SP keeps coming home to meet Abu.
Aslam
again
If you are home then keep an eye on the frame.
Are you in danger from this man?
Sir, from Javit Khanani and ISI in March 2005
Major Igbal, one of our ministers in Dubai
And after having a few meetings with his son a
Massive deal was funded in which this money
It was decided that from now on India too would have its own
currency no
Will start making it from the same British company
Due to which Pakistan is also a mess, why Lazarus?
our
Any amount of raw material of fake currency
He goes to Pakistan with this company.
that's why the quality is as good as
real but where did they get the plate January
Some of the MG 2005 Noto series in 2007
design changes were brought for which then
From Lazarus
Our minister and his son visited them from London.
Received delivery of plate and returned only
Found tactical flaws in his privateer jet
A few hours in Dubai
For and for we believe that these
within hours
want again
So these minictors, of the vertical minictors
By branding Chuta Manas, we are blacklisted.
Will get it done.
Sir, we cannot remain silent.
What is the most beautiful Adal?
she will come when the time comes
our time will also come
Leaving the house in five minutes. you
Don't worry, we will reach.
Alaafit. Or will search. Agreed. go inside rayman
Don't get angry with your brother. Yes. that mining bar
-Calls are being made from the bar site.
Dhunga.
Gayji please talk
do it
Is everything okay?
You were promised yours. malekumu
Khalam. Here sir. Ok.
It's very good. Anubhai. Here.
To check. with lit
Everything is the same. Here's the thing. hey ajmal
Ismail Bita. surf yes
Take up the case. ordered for you
He was busy with some work, that's why he didn't come.
Found. Send prayers.
You won't take it?
No Javid Bhai, now the boys will leave.
The luggage in the car will not increase, boy.
No, just wait for two minutes
even a grain of salt boys
Are you ready? Are many boys ready?
No boys, are you ready?
fighting
If you guys stay in the car then baby
will not survive
Jumme
It was the day's departure, yes, it was Friday's.
I was about to leave, someone came to know
Indian intelligence was already aware of our
Had digested the news of coming. that
we were ready
For.
until the elder says
fun
also
talk
is also
7 years of trust
You are instructing Saajj yes hey
Hindustani Mukbar is a big loser
If you beat me with a belt then you will cry hot.
Now I will make you my lap Roga
I will show you the attitude of the 1971 war.
later in pakistan
big
At that time Jiyavalak said something which
Bleed India will etch it in my mind
And we saw just such a fissure of the thousand
like a little
There is a small hole, I swear to God, this much
bad condition
I will do it for that country but for today
Tell me, how many infidel agents came with you?
is deproiled
Rachi Rawil Pindi Bol Son
hey
I don't want to kill you just tell me
Where are these agents and when did they come?
If you are angry in my country, tell me, tell me,
love
I am the family of Majdesh,
please inform the land brother as soon as possible
Arve Uder what's the matter child how are we today
Chamel Bhai has remembered, listen to me.
SP Aslam Rehman Bhai from Mai Kalokti bridge
Have you taken away Rehman? Has Rehman been taken away?
Oh you, don't worry baby, your Shamil
Uncle is sitting now, I will do it.
Chameel Bhai will take care of everything to collect the thread.
We will have to collect lati. We will have to collect lati.
to collect
will fall
To see your blood splattered on my shirt
Rehman Laket's blood is for it, Spi Saheb
excuse politely
12 to Tusane
All the people of Pyari are at work.
Put it. Tell them there's a Jeff's bank where
It's gone out somehow. I got news of that
Should continue to meet. Akhlaq.
Akhlaq. Also brother.
Are you going crazy? What did the child get?
news
In. how to do it
are taking
zaman
brother
to
a gift should also be given to you
You have such a deadly gaze, don't you?
Still don't come now, will you kiss me?
Yalina
you
Say no, I'm not helping.
Yalina leave the ball go to my house turn off your phone
Keep it and you will not come until I return.
I want Rahman's head first, then Lihari
Should.
I want your lies, at any cost
want and Rehman from his house
The responsibility of wearing a skirt alone woke me up
your fake feet and
If I listen to you today, don't go to those poor people now.
Parts of Muslim Movement Party
listen to
naked
So you have to take the goods here.
jameel
Sir, Pyamja Ali will vote. in an hour
Reman Bhai should be found at Sher Shapoor.
Otherwise this video will be on all TV channels tonight
Will make headlines. Next step and thinking
Forced not to do it. Cami, now your daughter's
life
It is also in my hands. Yalina!
Yalina!
Yelina, where are you?
Yalina! What is?
For Chilena?
chilean
You will take care of it, try, boy!
Lale's
location
I was just about to leave when your call came, yes
Don't let Aslam Raman rub you
Check the flowers. I want Rahman's head first,
Then you need a liar, someone in any
Should.
Where did this come from?
Add, if these videos load, then
My bowl will also be ruined, and my
Also needed. I can't hear you
subscribe
These schools were closed without permission
Or is it forbidden so let's come friend
Thank you for raising your brother, he is your Aslam.
You could kill your friends, let them know
What is a thousand needed?
A fire broke out from the Jyari task fort and the entire
After listening to Karachi. your
Forty officers kept digging the grave in jaggery.
Is. next
Orders kept going wrong. me rahman new sher shapoor
Digest.
Who is your Hamza among you?
come here
You set it on fire by throwing a spark
Have found Kavu.
Don't get this wrong fam pal. a pile of gunpowder here
you are sitting
To please the likes.
Where is your address given by Rikas Po?
When Jamil did not give, he was very worried.
yours
Why do you care about everything here?
Is it?
Brother, is this Jamil Jamali's daughter Bumara?
That day my boys keep saying,
Yalina Jamali, Yalina Jamali, Lambi Shran
What a blessing to you, Yashi,
Took Tadki home, was staying here, that's why
Now she is living at home,
Vizaara Jameel, I have left my daughter, now hurry up.
Inshala
Something will have to be done about this and Asyat Pappu.
You don't have to go to your home. you have to go
my house?
Why?
I didn't come back.
Has the mining money arrived?
Brother, six crores have arrived and the remaining six crores
As soon as our Fati comes, there is no Agra in Liari.
Your honor brother will not get your crown.
pakka and jer, hamzar
Let's go quickly, the best Lama is doing Misch.
yes friend friend
Loot Loot
Loot
To see what you can see
to see to see
to see
for
I couldn't move forward, move forward even as much as I can.
not sholay
Don't mind the palace until you leave the garden.
so
scare the ears
Remember if there is any Jew or foreigner in the room
So don't leave at all,
I, the woman, the children, the husband, all are infidels.
to everyone
I have to kill my lover, I have rejected all,
Don't do it at all.
Indian Commando Jandar comes from Panti Manzil
Are. ten twelve granat pekoe years
Are. panty floor
it would have been a few years
Are.
And don't dare to dare
Hey Inshan Rabhir, what should I say to you Pradhet?
Inshan aapka rabhir apni jeev anna rabhir
are the kings of life's sarpan
Hello, I have already talked to them. I
Was talking to a special agent.
you very very very very very very very very
very very very
a lot
We had spread the fear, had spread the wax earlier
Then do you want to say that it was 3rd October?
Chabbit is not of November
Chabid 11 has 309 different terrace attacks.
Messages to Intelligence Department
Had reached Cochin Mali Phoorsam Badi's
There was nothing wrong, there was too much head in the throat.
These guys have been caught, aren't they?
I tied it with my hands
Day locks, hope lurks in my house
after these
Kanani, Meir, Butori
Those who eat all this, these rich people
It's a little warmer than mine
Will burn the neighbor's house but its flames
your courtyard will be your center
Your arrest is one of ours in the enemy country.
such arrest
India will be proud all over the world
wait
do this game we are playing to win
But the most important thing to win this game
we have to survive
Where was Rajbar?
Where were you?
I'm tired of eating this pigeon
Kept waiting for you. meaning you
I am here, I will answer, I am in my father's house
I have left this for you.
Is there wine too?
Were with it?
any girl
do it do it do it
I want to become the king of the whole Karaji.
Come along if it's too late
Your fire will remain on me throughout the day.
after watching you
You won't ask me any questions if not.
So people the door is open
After today I will never have to leave home again.
threatened
My brothers of Lyari, today this is the end of Lyari.
seeing,
May the soul of my martyr Begum Benazir rest in peace.
must have gone
Our opponents probably remember
It would not be possible that once upon a time Laiyari had given me
by voting also
Like Jameel saab, here's M in Mukherjee
had done
That's why we are very happy today
Declaring that in the next election
from PAP
Pathi Peepal of my younger brother Rehman Balok
in amantmetti ittehaj
Worship of Liari after worshiping God
for us
It's a matter for everyone and if it's for a worship
I may have to get my head cut off too
So I am very happy.
Wahi Saheb called me younger brother.
blessed with honor
Instead of that my party People Jaman Committee is
Waga
Sir, she says that she will doom the PAP.
Will give her support.
The beautiful scene of Viyari is going to be changed by a bus.
Has been. Sadar Aaqib Alir of Pakistan
The courtier said in a surprising tone
It has been announced that his Pakistan Awami
Party next election Rehman Baloch's new party
Together with the Pepper Summons Committee
He is going to step into Aktiyasat
Is.
Man, this is still for mafia and knowledge
Even if it means a lot, it's too much for me.
Big scams come from the strong, now you will be punished.
will get
In response to our sins, your father
Don't you know?
are
our
So daughter, you were not at my house today.
Khaya Loda will give me advice
she is 19
There will be something for the three husbands at least not for Haya.
Good morning
Like a little girl who loves herself
Where did you understand?
When your mother gave birth to your body, then
I have been giving birth to the times since,
And why remember one thing, in this whole story
My blood speaks, I will teach for the sake of my father,
To keep this memory warm, have you ever
Rahman has to look like Imay,
You have always shared with people who
By becoming more powerful than you at any time
Liari can be snatched from Liari
If you want to maintain your dominance then this Rahman and
Put such a person in place of Arshit
do
did you lift the veil did you lift the veil
it's done
Pickly
Neither Jahara nor Khura nor Tara Dil is innocent.
make gold
Kar liye saatha pasoom zahara niyat noorani saatha
if there is a mole then it is a canal
But you know about it in hindsight.
I won't hide even a single story
Chakhawa Paanu Sharal Sakhawa Jab Mera
Meri Zain Noctor Jarwari Sahab's Specials
Is it cancer?
Whatever you recommended after 21-11
there is inflation
When I am no more
If India had talked to us then God forbid.
I swear Delhi on its killing years. here you
When you've eaten, order something. hey brother doone
Yes. Come you are more guru. Brother, after having children,
Have children, brother. hey come my friend our hamza
with
also
More Indians seek help from America
Kept asking and America also kept showing carrots
As Ayatay thinks that with Kashmir
with
Punjab's way should be rekindled
So August 15th
Some Mazda like Mumba in Americor
fee to do
Hey, we are always ready in the strength of the permanent.
Brother, please send the list to Uzair.
Yo Gumball, the goods will arrive before time.
I said yes, I am happy to see the date.
to you
Go ahead and let me do it.
nine
August keeps saying and nothing on this day
Is. That day after talking to Shirani Sahad
Can pick up.
You will get all the items on the night of Naugat.
very nice.
Reman
Brother. Took a photo with everyone.
Get up brother. If you do, then get up.
If you live with him then you are in the first marriage.
Yours. This uncle is not your mother's daughter.
Marriage.
Where women are worried
ke min tupkha jubkha jubkha jubkha
The things about Diya Lagra Khadar
You woke up well in the light of the lamp of light.
Your movement has become less powerful due to the weight of the body.
you decide
truth is worthless
Kotri border is still needed in the next nine days
but you will get it later
If you have any question after seeing this lit, you can
Tell me if Ahman Bhai Mashrut lives?
Jundari see you
now
Till our peter children are killed
Kulay Saiwals drowned in school water
mixed up
I am sorry sir, I am surprised. What?
I had no idea about this thing. no,
No, no, there is no issue. I am Rahman
I ask my brother. What happened?
I am coming Shirani sir, reached Kotri border.
Live with. me so
leaf
Just like this, every time it eats, it hurts me a lot.
Are you or have you ever been on the phone with similar blows?
I have brought the key to the toddy.
Even then you will have to do Lyari before doing anything.
It will have to be done once Lyari does something, then you
So nothing can be done and the blackest
The circle and the nearby forest are awake
If the pool is being tied on Bastan then it is enough
There was traffic. laskhan
Who is in charge?
Qasim was stuck on the Pakistani signal.
Reach Lyari Expressway.
Ujair
Where is the car?
Brother, Uzair is a cotridge, she is the one with Amrit Sir.
Original delivery
Today's date was fixed for the day of marriage.
I told you, brother, you were the one who said it.
Well, it will happen during the night, in two-three hours.
will reach
Looking at the date it says 9th August.
day nothing
I have to stop the snake and stop it.
here
I want to control the kilometer meter.
form
I won't trust you alive in front of me
He is breathing, that's his reason, hey too.
Okay, he is a Baloch and so is my son-in-law.
Now he understands that if he has been lied to
If we get Kaddi, then the reins of Karachi are ours.
hogi in hand and reins of karachi means
all over Pakistan
Bhaluj, if you betray me, then
I will kill you before killing you
I will make it. And Jamil sir, thank you very much.
do it
Must not survive, must not survive
want
Will handle it, run.
come come come come come
survive the quest to reach the city
Should. He keeps his finger angry in the cows, right?
Died early.
You people's chance, the disease has come, the disease is screwing,
disease
Ajay to Ajay to Ajay
Ajay
to
Keep your eyes open brother, nothing to you
I won't let anything happen to you brother.
you
run away
ran away
do it do it do it
two
Hamza Bhai Rahman Bhai engaged in himself
Thakar was running away. Hamza Bhai did his best
To save Rahman Bhai. but
Who pleases Allah...
It has been learned from Daraya that Rahman
Vapor on a political platform in your car
Lived in the forest near the circular road
The killer from his car at a roadblock
Even before starting the baramat uchcha
Rahman Duckett and his men
And till he got to Liari Gendal Hospital
It was delivered, that blood is worth more waste.
Died. Big outside the hospital right now
There is an atmosphere of panic. idol ataman of the people
Has been. Dehman's resident god of his death
answer
Durandar area area area
area
that directly or indirectly this world
I am getting into almost every terrorist
Pakistan's hand behind it. whenever
Pakistani
ISI from any terrorist organization
If India gets attacked, then arms and
Where do ammunition checkwires?
Camels underweight. Russian guns
Amerikroon's name Hida our name
do it
If there is international investigation then ISI
These ganks should not be named
By infiltrating their mass and
Cut off terrorists and ISI
Intel will keep telling us first hand about this
Criminals in operation
we might just have a killing machine in
our hands.
You are guilty till this very moment.
When I behave, it is called living.
This love will happen, this is love, this is love, this is love
Ishq hai ishq love this love ishq hai ishq
By the way, no one could stop me from loving my heart.
dagger blocked by a sword
That ignorance of Ishq Majmu is not gone
This is a new India, it will also enter the house and
will also kill