[♪ Lizzo sings "Juice"]
♪
Mirror, mirror on the wall
-♪
don't say it 'cause I know I'm cute
♪
-♪
Ooh, baby
♪
Louis down to my drawers
-♪
LV all on my shoes
♪
-♪
Ooh, baby
♪
It ain't my fault
that I'm out here getting loose
♪
Gotta blame it on the Goose
Gotta blame it on my juice, baby
♪
It ain't my fault
that I'm out here making news
♪
-[arrow whooshing]
-[alarm clock beeping]
♪
I'm the pudding in the proof
Gotta blame it on my juice
♪
Ya-ya-ee
Ya-ya-ee, ya-ya-ee...
[Leah]
The question isn't
"Who's gonna let me?"
It's "Who's gonna stop me?"
Nobody, boo. That's who.
♪
Ya-ya-ee, ya-ya-ee, ya-ya-ee
-[grunts]
-♪
Blame it on my juice
♪
Blame it, blame it on my juice...
[sighs] Today is the day!
-♪
Look, baby, I'm the whole meal
♪
-♪
Ooh, baby
♪
-♪
David, you ain't being slick...
-[vehicle door closes]
[squeals]
This is it!
-Hi!
-[laughter]
God willing, you could be
the first female showrunner at Media Core!
How do you feel?
[sighs] Like everything
I've pinned my hopes and dreams on
and worked so hard for
is finally happening.
-Yeah.
-So, you know,
-no big deal.
-Yeah.
♪
Blame it on my juice, yeah
♪♪
-[exclaims]
-[laughter]
-[elevator bell chimes]
-[singsongy] Leah!
My boss, our queen, the metric
of excellence for which we all aspire to.
-Thank you, darling. Extra shot?
-You know it.
And, Brenda, you don't even need
hair and makeup.
You are camera-ready
and flawless as always.
Oh, Roland, I love your honesty.
-[Treese clears throat]
-Good morning, Treese.
-Here you go.
-Excuse me.
You ran out of compliments? [chuckles]
That's crazy, 'cause I know I look cute.
[scoffs]
-[Leah] I need those dog graphics.
-[Roland] Dan said we're over
-by four minutes and 12 seconds.
-I know.
I'm cutting the food segment.
No one likes cauliflower fronting as rice.
Objection. I like cauliflower rice.
-Do you, though?
-I do.
I'm all for a versatile vegetable.
Can broccoli be rice?
Can carrots be a steak?
-Cauli gets all my needs.
-Love that for you.
And Dan's office confirmed your meeting.
[singsongy] Love that for you.
[playful grunting]
-And then one more thing.
-Yes.
Your dad wanted me to clear your calendar
for March 3rd.
For the thing I'm definitely not doing?
Mm-hmm, yep. I'm-a stop talking now.
Did you hear that? I didn't, either.
Because nothing was said. No words.
-Silence. Glorious silence.
-Uh-huh.
I love your promotion shoes.
-[grunts] Let's go.
-[Leah]
Dream team!
Does everyone have the revised rundown?
Got it, Leah. Thirty seconds to air.
-Is the roll-in piece up from edit?
-[assistant director]
Standing by.
-[Dan] We're leading with the ducks.
-[director] All right, everybody!
-[Brenda] Oh, thank you.
-[director] Quiet, quiet. We're going.
[Leah] All right, everyone.
Last looks are good.
Yes, yes. We're good.
-Have a good one, Leah.
-Let's have a great show.
-[news theme playing]
-[director]
In five, four, three,
two...
-[assistant director] One. Cue.
-[news theme ends]
Good morning. This is
Better Day USA.
-I'm Brenda Phelps.
-And I'm Ted Davies.
[Brenda] And we have a lot of fun
happening in the studio today,
but first let's take a look at some news.
[lighthearted music playing]
[Dan] Leah, after 30 years
at this network,
I thought stepping down to spend more time
with my family was gonna be tough, but--
You still don't remember
your grandkids' names?
-Not a chance.
-[laughs]
-So--
-I know this is hard, Dan.
I can't imagine doing this show
without you.
You haven't just been my boss,
you've been a mentor.
And a wonderful friend.
Great. Now it's even harder.
[Dan sighs]
You're not gonna like this.
Wait. What is going on?
The higher-ups want to bring in
another candidate
before they decide
who's best for the role.
-What?!
-Look, your record is stellar.
Your-your work speaks for itself, okay?
But--
But?
There are some concerns about
your ability to be a team player.
Look, this is not my call.
I'm sorry, okay?
Leah, unfortunately, this is above me.
Nothing is above you!
Now, where was that attitude
when you were questioning
every one of my decisions
for the past 15 years?
I'm nothing but a team player.
I've devoted my life to this show.
I speak in chyrons.
I wake up at 3:00 in the morning.
I am an owl.
So, if I'm not the obvious choice, who?
Who?
Hmm?
That owl call was unintentional.
They're bringing in Jarrett Roy.
They just poached him from NBC's
Nightly.
[sighs]
So, I didn't get the job.
Now it's between me and Jarrett Roy.
That really fine guy, right? From NBC?
-You know, they say that he's--
-[kicks]
-[Leah] The worst.
-Ow! Why'd you do that?
Leah and Jarrett have history.
It was before your time.
Like history history?
Just the kind you don't want to repeat.
Moving on. Next topic.
I saw the press called you a WAG again.
-What's a WAG?
-They're the supportive wives
and girlfriends of high-profile players.
But I am not Ayden Young's arm candy.
[Leah] No, you are not.
But it's yet another reminder
that I'm just a girlfriend, not a wife.
And that's why I have a list.
But... [stammers] you're single.
Like I said, it works.
-You know what doesn't work?
-Hmm?
You not spilling the tea.
So, what happened with her and Jarrett?
[Brenda sighs]
So, Jarrett and Leah used to work
in their first newsrooms together.
And it's--
[clears throat]
Oh, come-- And?
And we dated.
I fell for him.
He made me feel like
we had something special,
-then he cheated on me...
-No!
...with a P.A. named Kimmy.
Yeah. It really hurt.
Jarrett was Leah's first love.
-I wouldn't say love.
-[Treese] Oh.
I was young, didn't know any better.
Lesson learned.
Oh, mama, is that why
you created The List?
That's why "no cheaters" is on The List.
-Okay, let's see.
-[phone clicks]
-Yo.
-Okay.
-"College graduate..."
-Mm-hmm.
"...no kids, no mouth breathers"?
-[exhales heavily]
-Oh.
Oh, yeah, got it. That makes sense.
"At least six feet tall
but no more than six-four."
I don't want to strain my neck
looking up at him.
[Treese] No, I kind of get that.
"Has a 401(k)." Seriously? Who has that?
Me. And my future man.
[Treese] "Proper dental hygiene"?
-What?
-I dated a guy with furry teeth.
Oh, I remember him.
-Brad.
-Ew.
Look, I know what I want,
and I know what I don't.
Honey, it's great to know what you want,
but there are no men on this planet
who will have all, what,
70 of the qualities on that list?
Look, I know you're disappointed,
but everything's gonna work out.
God has a plan.
His plan hasn't worked out
so well for me in the past.
Girl.
I'm sorry.
No shade to you, but I'm worried.
This was supposed to be a done deal.
But now I have to face off against a man
with zero experience
in morning television,
but he's a man.
A man who was born on third base
because gender politics
and double standards
and our toxic butthole of a patriarchy!
Down with the patriarchy!
Get it, girls!
Rage!
-[hisses]
-Ooh. Oh, oh.
-[Leah] Oh, my God.
-[laughs]
All I know is the last thing I'd ever want
is happening to me:
Jarrett Roy is back in my life
and coming for my job.
[lighthearted music playing]
[exhales heavily]
Can I be honest?
I don't think she works here.
♪ ♪
[siren wailing in distance]
[breathlessly] Leah! Damn.
I need to do more cardio.
Do you Peloton
or are you all about that core?
Sorry, not the point.
He's here.
Okay.
Come on.
-[excited chatter]
-[energetic music playing]
-[♪ Salt-N-Pepa sings
"Whatta Man - Rerecorded"]
-♪
Yeah
♪
What a man, what a man, what a man,
what a mighty good man
♪
-♪
He's a mighty, mighty
♪
-♪
Ooh
♪
good man
Yeah, talk to me
♪
Yeah, ooh
What a man, what a man, what a man,
what a mighty good man
♪
He's a mighty, mighty good man
What a man, what a man, what a man
♪
-♪
what a mighty good man
♪
-♪
Uh, all right
♪
Gotta say it again now
♪♪
Good morning, everyone.
Dan Milken. We spoke on the phone.
-Welcome to the team.
-[Jarrett] Thanks.
[Dan] Leah, I'd like
to introduce you to J--
Jarrett Roy.
Graduated magna cum laude from Harvard.
Known as the Prince of Prime Time,
a nickname he may or may not
have given himself.
Has almost two decades in nightly news
under his belt, and here he is.
Wow. Thank you for
that, uh, glowing intro, Leah.
It's good to see you ag--
[Jarrett clears throat]
Uh, okay.
Leah, you never mentioned
that you two knew each other.
We, uh...
Barely.
It was a long time ago.
[Dan] Mm-hmm. Okay.
I'm gonna give, uh, Jarrett the tour,
and then he can stop by your office.
It's the corner one with the sick view.
-[sighs]
-[Dan] Let's go this way.
So, how tall are you?
-Uh, about six-three.
-Wow.
That has got to be the finest man
who is not on-air talent.
I am shook. Where is the Victorian era
fainting couch when you need it?
Whose team are you guys on?
-Yours.
-Obviously.
But those soulful eyes, that chiseled
jawline and those washboard abs--
[Treese] How did you see his abs?
I created a finsta and deep-creeped
his feed like any self-respecting human.
Mm. I'm-a need to see a visual.
Wow. So they're, like, stacked.
-But also, like, carved.
-Good God.
-Don't do it.
-Thank you.
[knock on door]
[Jarrett] Leah.
Come in. Have a seat.
I just wanted to say that morning TV is
a very different beast from prime time,
but I'm sure you'll probably find a way
to be a value-add.
[chuckles softly]
Look, I know you don't want me here.
Our personal history aside--
-Ancient history.
-Got it.
And let me be clear.
I don't care.
-Clear.
-Hmm.
But I'd be pissed, too, if I thought
I was a lock for showrunner
and the execs brought in
another contender in the 11th hour.
So, thank you for being the bigger person
and making sure I'm settling in all right.
I'm welcoming you
because this is my house,
and that's the kind of polite
and hospitable thing I was raised to do.
I'm not encouraging you to settle in.
That's how you want to play it?
-No other way.
-Then I'll warn you.
It's been my goal to run my own show.
I want this job, and I...
go after what I want.
Oh, I remember.
And, Jarrett?
Your pathetic little attention-grab,
it's a quarter-inch higher on the right.
Damn, she's right.
[clears throat]
[lighthearted music playing]
Oh! Oh, oh, oh.
-[Leah clears throat]
-Hi.
Everybody's met Jarrett.
Yes. Definitely.
Okay. So, we got sweeps coming up, right?
And I want to crush
Today, Good Morning America,
everybody.
So let's hear your pitches
for Valentine's Day.
Unbelievable true-life love stories
that really warm the heart.
Uh, we did it three years ago.
My heart's not warm.
Okay, but one guy found love
-and a kidney online.
-[Dan] What else?
Love from beyond the grave.
We can have a medium communicate
with loved ones that have passed.
Mm, too niche. Dead love doesn't rate.
How about old but not dead yet people?
Uh, we could ask elderly couples
their tips for keeping their love alive.
Yeah, like pacemakers?
Leah, what do you have?
Let's look at how
this so-called holiday even started.
You want to do an exposé? On love?
Love isn't hype and pressure
and performative displays on social media
by people trying to prove their worth
based on likes and dollars.
You're right.
Love is the root of happiness,
compassion, self-worth and...
[both] Social justice.
Ooh.
So, we take down Valentine's Day.
Then what?
For the Fourth of July,
we, uh, choose England's side?
[laughter]
[Dan] While I sympathize with you, Leah--
I personally have spent
a small fortune at Cartier,
uh, thanks to
this quote-unquote "holiday"--
perhaps we should opt for a little more...
something mainstream.
Think I might have something.
This book changed my life.
And I know it'll help others.
Jarrett's book report?
That's our Valentine's Day story?
[others chuckling]
Okay, uh, Michael Todd...
Michael Todd is a pastor
from Tulsa, Oklahoma,
best-selling author
and a YouTube phenomenon,
and it all started with this book.
It's about helping people succeed in love
by using their faith.
Jarrett, we try to maintain
a secular POV here at the show.
Well, except for Christmas,
Easter, Halloween.
-Halloween isn't religious.
-It is if you're Wiccan.
[Jarrett] Uh, okay, look, I-I know this is
slightly left of center, but faith--
come on, guys, faith is hotter than ever.
People struggle
with love and relationships,
but isn't a meaningful connection
what we all want?
-Yeah.
-[Jarrett] This book offers up
solid, relatable advice.
It's the real deal.
And so are Michael and his wife Natalie.
"How to Win at Dating, Marriage and Sex."
Sex definitely rates.
Lot of people are fans of that.
You're not actually considering this?
This is outside of our usual wheelhouse,
but I want to go out with a bang.
-Let's do it.
-[Curtis] Okay, everybody.
Let's get out there and bang.
That came out wrong. I hear it now.
All right, Leah,
you're gonna produce this with Jarrett.
What? We don't need
two senior producers on this.
And why? It's my story.
Leah recently pointed out to me
that when we challenge each other,
we reach the best outcomes.
Teamwork.
I love teamwork.
[lighthearted music playing]
-Good night.
-Good night, Leah.
-Heading out?
-[sighs]
No, just going for an elevator ride.
You always kept me on my toes.
Well, enjoy it for the five weeks
and three days you have left here.
Okay, are we gonna spar like this
the whole time?
If so, I need to cancel
my Sunday pickup games
and save my competitive edge
for our spicy little chats.
Or here's an idea.
We keep the dialogue to a minimum
and avoid each other as much as possible.
You don't have to be salty just 'cause
I got the jump on you with this story.
I'm not.
I'm excited to see
how your off-brand appreciation
for this Internet preacher pans out
or crashes and burns.
Ah, don't be like that, Caldwell.
-Hmm.
-You got something against God?
Just people who use Him to get a leg up.
I'm not using anyone.
This book changed me.
I hadn't thought about how cheating
and being messy was jamming me up.
[scoffs] So you're telling me you're
a reformed player, thanks to this book?
Yes. Absolutely.
My player card has been revoked.
Look, it's a great book
and a slam-dunk story,
so either shoot the ball
or ride the bench, Le-Le.
-Don't call me that again.
-[elevator bell dings, doors open]
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
[button clicks]
Good night, Le-Le.
-She still wants me.
-[button clicks]
[Leah]
I can't stand him.
He's a king narcissist
who doesn't have one ounce of humility.
He thinks he's always right.
[chuckles] And you don't?
I'm nothing like Jarrett.
[chuckles] I must have you confused
for another friend
who thinks she's always right.
I can't help it if I'm usually right.
Usually?
Often.
Always.
[chuckles] Okay,
we'll keep that between us.
Just remember what Dan said.
I have to show the higher-ups
I can play well with others. I know.
And you will.
Just keep your cool.
Don't let Jarrett get under your skin.
I'm sure that's what he wants.
To get a rise out of me,
knock me off my game.
Little does he know,
-I'm going scorched earth!
-[door closes]
Oh, hey, girl, Ayden just got home.
I got to go.
-Love you.
-Love you, too.
Hey, baby. You busy?
Oh. No. Not at all.
[chuckles] I can give you
as much time as you need.
Okay. Come take a seat.
-[sighs heavily]
-[uplifting music playing]
-Oh! [gasps]
-[chuckles]
Boom.
Just got it out of the repair shop.
-Your championship ring.
-Mm-hmm.
Polished it a little.
You know, it's kind of crazy
this'll probably be my last one.
Yeah, I'm not gonna get a ring
when I'm calling games next season.
[sighs] I know it's tough
when you don't know what the future holds.
Well... what would I do without you?
Hmm?
[both chuckle]
-Mwah.
-Huh.
All right, so, gonna put this in the safe.
-Yeah.
-Make sure she knows I cherish her.
-Yep. Yep. Yep.
-Right? Okay. All right.
-[chuckles] Okay.
-I'm gonna take a shower.
-Okay. [chuckles]
-I'll be back.
[groaning]
[message chirps]
[chuckles softly]
-Okay, we have that in common, fitness.
-Yeah.
-Do you like running?
-Oh, my God, I love running.
I just finished running
the Boston Marathon last year,
and I'm training to do New York next.
-Wow, I just love me a good marathon.
-Mm-hmm.
Like, 40 miles? Easy, right?
-Give me 60. [laughing]
-[chuckles]
-[phone beeping]
-Uh...
Oh. It's probably just my trainer.
[stammers] Go ahead, take it.
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah.
Actually, do you mind
if I just... really...
-Just got to use the washroom real quick.
-No, that's fine.
I'll be right here.
[♪ Brian Brown sings "The World Is Yours"]
[phone clicks, beeps]
[message chirps]
-[waiter] Hi.
-Hi.
He paid the bill.
Would you still like your food?
What do you...
[stammers] He left?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll just get it to go.
-Of course.
-Cool. Thank you.
[laughs] I'm gonna die alone.
-[Brenda]
Good morning.
-[news theme plays]
This is
Better Day USA.
Welcome back.
Now, while the human event business
remains bustling,
many people are getting in on the fun
by throwing birthday parties,
obedience school graduations and
even elaborate weddings for their pets.
Dogs are getting wifed up,
and I cannot find a man.
This is my life, you guys.
You've spent a lot of time and money...
I played with the order for the photos.
You'll see,
it's much more dynamic this way.
It better be, since I don't have time
to change it back.
Let's just hope our special guests
stay on their marks, guys.
[singsongy] Took care of that, too.
Taped the treats to the floor.
[Brenda] Oh, I love the little hat.
-It's party time.
-So cute. And how about yours?
Did you think, uh, your dog enjoyed
his graduation day as much?
Oh, definitely.
Spiral is enthusiastic about everything.
[Ted chuckles]
-[Ted] Hi, Spiral. Oh, yeah. Oh.
-[Brenda] Oh. Oh.
-That is enthusiasm. Yeah. [chuckles]
-Oh. Oh.
[Ted] Okay, well,
that's a lot of enthusiasm.
-See, she likes you.
-[Ted] Yeah.
-More than my ex-wife. [chuckles]
-Oh.
[Brenda] Maybe we can get a little help
-for my cohost.
-That'd be great.
[laughter]
[Brenda] We got a loose dog on set!
It's morning TV, live.
-You never know what's gonna happen.
-[dog growls, barks]
-Live TV, folks.
-[Ted chuckles]
That's right.
-[Brenda]
We got a loose dog on set!
-[laughing]
[dogs barking on phone]
Photos were good, right?
[phone clicks, video stops]
Let's jump in.
I drafted a list of interview questions
for Michael Todd.
That's it?
No small talk? A little tête-à-tête?
That's French.
Je suis pas intéressée.
That was impressive.
Can we focus and figure out this bad idea
you convinced my boss to sign off on?
Okay, our boss.
And you're still on that?
Did you even read the book?
All this book's doing is
dusting off the Scriptures
and dressing up the Bible
with some down-home lingo
and acting like it has all the answers.
Well, at least it has some answers.
Besides, Michael Todd's not
the only pastor presenting the Gospel
in a relevant and progressive way,
but he's the one that's straight fire.
Fire-fire-fire.
On YouTube.
Let's just do the work and have our booker
reach out to Michael Todd's team
to see when he can fly in
for the interview.
Oh, no, I already spoke to Dan.
We're clear for next weekend
to go to Tulsa.
-Excuse me?
-Yeah.
We need to see the pastor in his element.
His family, his church, his followers,
the whole shebang.
[phone chimes]
Um, where are you going?
What do you care? You seem to have
forgotten we're producing this together.
You know, fine.
I'll see you later tonight
for drinks with Dan.
He invited you?
Super.
[laughing]
No need to dance around it.
I know you called Roland to see about
clearing my schedule March 3rd.
-Yes, I did.
-Mm.
I want you to come to the cemetery
with me this year.
[wistful music playing]
[Leah chuckles softly]
I paid my respects at the funeral.
If you want to go, I get that,
but it's not for me.
It would mean a lot to me
for us to honor your mother together.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I don't want to upset you,
but I can't go there.
Leah, you've been throwing yourself
into work ever since we lost her.
But you can't outrun grief.
Mourning is a process.
It would help if we just...
if we just go there and sit with the pain
than to try to shut it out.
I love you, and this banana pudding
is so bomb, but...
[sighs] I don't have time
to deal with this right now.
I have a man to destroy.
You're dating someone?
What?
[♪ Duncan Hamilton sings
"My Soul Says Yes"]
[lively chatter]
Where's Dan?
[phone chimes]
[Dan recorded]
Sorry, guys,
something came up at the last minute.
I trust you'll make good use
of the bonding time.
-[laughing]
-[phone beeps]
He played us.
He sure did.
I guess now's a good chance
to catch up outside of the office.
Hmm.
How is it, anyway, that we've never run
into each other once in all these years?
Easy. I don't hang out at places
with lemon pepper wings
and stacks of one-dollar bills.
Wow. That-that was quick.
I-I ain't even see the gun.
I've also avoided you, since I've had
no desire for our paths to cross.
Yeah, uh, about that.
Back then, I was young and foolish,
but I learned that real manhood
is found in commitment.
-Really?
-Yes.
How so?
Are you in a committed relationship?
Well, not yet.
Meaning you're still a player.
It's not one or the other.
I'm... dating with a purpose.
I want something real.
That's the new you?
Okay, look.
Kimmy was a thing that happened.
[sighs]
It's not who I am, never was.
I am truly sorry I hurt you.
But I'm walking a different path now.
I'm supposed to believe that?
Buy into this Jarrett 2.0 nonsense?
Be all buddy-buddy with you
while you come for my job?
I-I'm just trying to bury the hatchet.
[sighs] Easy for you to say when you're
trying to take something else from me.
If you're really sorry, quit.
That's what I thought.
-Two things can be true at once, Leah.
-[sighs]
I want this job...
and I'm sorry.
Okay, where are you going?
What about bonding?
I can get along with everyone.
Okay, uh, are you-you trying to
convince me, or is someone else listening?
[sighs] I need a drink.
And I already took the liberty
of ordering for us.
Whiskey, rocks?
Oh, we won't be needing that one.
Then, cosmo for the lady.
Cosmo's for me, my guy.
Yeah. [sighs]
-You remembered my drink?
-[Jarrett] Of course.
I remember everything about you.
And you really ordered a cosmo?
Okay, I am a confident Black man.
And it's a delicious drink.
You might want to put your pinky down.
[woman over P.A.]
Boarding
will begin shortly
-at Gate 55 for Tulsa, Oklahoma.
-
[busy chatter]
[Brenda] Tulsa is where I won
my first beauty pageant.
-[Treese gasps] Yes! Wow.
-Tulsa, here we come.
I just love giving up my precious
few minutes of free time over the weekend
for this fool's errand.
Oh! And did I tell you what Dan did?
Is it worse than me getting ghosted?
-Oh, no.
-You got ghosted?
-Oh.
-The food didn't even come, and he left.
[Jarrett] Excuse me. Excuse me. Yes, yes.
We're-we're all traveling together.
Thank you.
We are not. We don't know this man!
-Hi, Jarrett.
-Hi, Brenda.
How are you, Treese?
[laughing]
-He's so funny.
-[chuckles]
And, Leah, so what are
you gonna do next, huh?
Tell airport security I'm smuggling
something suspicious in my bag?
Don't tempt me with a good time.
Funny you should say that,
because Roland booked us together,
so apparently he thinks I'm a good time.
3A, huh?
Well, would you look at that. 3B.
Nice!
Roland better be updating his LinkedIn.
See you on the plane, queen.
[lighthearted music playing]
-Thank you.
-Amazing. Amazing. Do you want--
-You look fantastic. [chuckles]
-[Natalie] Oh.
Is that a glow or God?
[laughs] Just kidding.
-[laughing]
-[cameraperson] We're rolling.
-[Brenda] All right, you guys ready?
-Let's do it.
[Brenda]
With love in the spotlight
on Valentine's Day,
I'm here with
New York Times
best-selling author
Michael Todd and his lovely wife Natalie.
Thanks for joining us.
-We're so happy to be here.
-We're happy to be here.
-Oh.
-This should be good.
-It's going to be great.
Now, Michael, why do you think
your message about relationships
has continued to resonate
with people so strongly?
Well, Brenda, I think it's because
relationships are hard.
Dating is hard.
Especially with all the constant messages
that we're getting on social media and TV,
the images, which makes it harder.
-Yeah.
-And this message is
-to really help people find their aim.
-I love it.
I am sensitive to lactose,
and this shit is cheesy.
Then pop a Lactaid.
This isn't a takedown.
[Michael]
Fixing your aim is actually
changing the focus from the superficial
and putting the focus on
the things that actually really matter
to make a successful relationship.
-[Brenda] Wow.
-[Michael] What are their core values?
-Do they actually have character?
-Mm-hmm.
This is one thing I've found out,
is you can't Facebook faithfulness,
and you cannot Instagram integrity.
Great.
Enough with the softballs, Brenda.
[Jarrett]
Ignore her, Brenda.
Ask him,
what if someone's aim is off
but they think they're doing fine?
[Brenda]
What if a person is
dating around and they don't think
they need to change?
Well, then I got to talk about
chicken nuggets.
-[laughs] Okay.
-Now, just go with me for a second.
-Chicken nuggets?
-Imagine that there was
chicken nuggets being passed around,
and everybody is putting
their beautiful hands into this bucket,
touching them, nibbling on them,
taking pieces
and then putting it back in there.
-Ugh.
-The question is:
Would you want
one of those chicken nuggets?
No, I would not. [laughing]
Oh, my God. [chuckles]
I'm a nugget?
...but I promise you,
it's gonna leave you feeling empty.
What if that person's just empty?
-Or what if they're full of it?
-[Brenda]
That's why you recommend
-dating intentionally, right?
-[Michael] Yes.
Okay, talk to me about that.
You're not just going after every guy
that's cute and cut up...
Mm.
...or every baddie with a body.
Ooh, as tempting as it may be.
-Dig deeper, Brenda.
-[Jarrett] Ignore her and stay on track.
Don't listen to him!
[Jarrett]
Why are you
all up in my mic, yo?
Because you're only using it
to make a glorified promo reel.
This isn't
To Catch a Predator.
-Okay? Teamwork makes the dream work.
-Uh...
-[arguing continues]
-So, this really sounds wise, right?
All of this advice, but...
Ask him if he thinks he's oversimplifying
-relationship dynamics.
-[Jarrett]
Jesus, take the wheel.
-You're impossible.
-[Brenda] Relationships--
Well, you're a walking red flag
who's afraid of commitment!
And you're a narcissistic perfectionist
who's as stubborn as an ox.
How 'bout that?
Goodbye.
Look what you did!
Okay, you've been trying
to trash this story from the start.
So, what if one person wants
to get married, though,
and the other person doesn't?
Asking for a Frienda.
If you've been dating
three, four, five, God forbid, six years
-and there's no forward momentum...
-[Natalie] Mm-hmm.
[Michael] ...you need to step back
and ask yourself:
Is this the relationship
that God wants me to be in?
Is this God's will for my life?
And maybe you need to ask
the even tougher question:
Does this relationship need to end?
Brenda, are you okay?
I just need to pray on this
and sort myself out.
It's just one man's opinion.
Yeah, maybe. I don't know.
I have to be honest.
The thing that I keep worrying about is:
Is it God's will, and is it time
to end the relationship?
I'm sorry.
Ladies, we are not okay.
You're a mess. You're a mess. I'm a mess.
We are all three hot messes, okay?
This book is speaking to me.
I've been reading it.
-You mean decorating it?
-[Treese] I'm being serious.
I think that we all need to fix our aim.
Yeah, I'm-I'm good.
My aim is...
-[blows softly]
-[Treese] Yeah?
When's the last time you dated someone?
Yeah, like, actually dated,
more than a week or two,
'cause you never give anyone a chance.
Work is my focus,
but if I found someone who fit The List--
-The List.
-The List. Yes, we know.
It is my masterpiece in progress
guiding me towards my perfect man.
This book says that
you need to rip up The List.
I'm not ripping up anything.
Do you know how long
it's taken me to curate that?
What if all the things that you think
you want are actually holding you back?
You are really drinking the Kool-Aid.
Yeah. I'm chugging it.
-[chuckles]
-Okay, look.
"Have you ever known a girl
who dated pretty much any guy
who happened to show an interest in her
without ever stopping to think about
the kind of guy
who would really be right for her?"
Mm.
"Or a couple
who have dated for a long time
and have gotten so comfortable with it
that they aren't making
any move towards marriage?"
Ooh, that book is a wake-up call.
[chuckles]
You know, I-I was really trying to be
the "go with the flow" chick,
but I can't do that anymore.
And I can't just keep going out
with every guy who swipes right.
Mm.
I got to try this.
Chapter four. It's the nugget chapter.
"Intentional Dating."
Yep. And I need to reread chapter five:
"Does It Need to End?"
-Seriously, nothing speaks to you?
-[scoffs]
Like the chapter about
unpacking to repack?
You don't think that
you need to fix your aim?
While I appreciate the concern,
my aim is clear.
I'm going to kick Jarrett Roy to the curb,
land my promotion,
break the glass ceiling,
and then everything will be great.
But first, I can't believe
I have to spend my Sunday alone, here,
shooting B-roll with that a-hole.
-[♪ Transformation Worship sings "Yahweh"]
-♪
You are Jehovah
♪
-[lively chatter]
-♪
I stand in awe
♪
I stand in awe of You
-♪
Nothing You can't do
♪
-♪
There's nothing You can't do
♪
The Great I Am
We know who You are
♪
Sovereign Redeemer
-♪
All power's in Your hands
♪
-♪
All power's in Your hands
♪
-♪
Don't have to understand
♪
-♪
Don't have to understand
♪
-♪
God, here I am, yeah
♪
-♪
God, here I am
♪
Come on, we say, this one thing I know
This one thing I know
♪
I put my faith in You,
I put my faith in You
♪
You are in control
Great I Am, we call Your name, oh
♪
-♪
Yahweh
♪
-♪
Yahweh
♪
-♪
Reign over
♪
-♪
Reign over
♪
-♪
Take over
♪
-♪
Take over
♪
'Cause it's not finished, no
Come on. If you believe it's not finished,
would you just lift that up right now?
♪
It's not finished, no
♪♪
Impressive, right?
Today, I want to talk to you
about the future.
God wants all of us
to go to another level,
but to see that future, you're gonna
have to stop dwelling on the past.
He wants you to be free from the things,
the people, the places, the ideas
that have been holding you back.
He's saying, "Let the past go."
-Stretch for the new.
-[congregation murmurs agreement]
Stretch for more.
And you got to grab ahold
of all of the great things
that God has waiting just for you.
[cheering and applause]
Mm.
Bad news. Storm's hitting early.
Ugh, we should have left
with everyone else.
We have to get back to New York.
We have a show in the morning.
I told the weather that. I promise I did.
But the county issued a tornado warning.
-Welcome to The Sooner State.
-[scoffs]
And the sooner we get to the airport
and out of here, the better.
♪
Womp, womp, wah
♪♪
[chuckles] There is no way
our flight isn't going to be canceled.
-You don't know that.
-[mocking] "You don't know that."
[phones chime and ding]
Uh, I wonder who that could be.
"We've canceled your flight"? Ugh.
"Due to forecasted
severe weather conditions."
-What?
-Uh, bong.
Love to say "I told you so."
Look, I rented a car.
There's a flight leaving
out of Memphis later.
-Memphis? How far is that?
-Six hours.
Or... you can stay here
and get eaten by a tornado.
-[♪ J.J. Fad sings "Supersonic"]
-♪
Supersonic
♪
Your call.
Supersonic
♪
[frustrated grunt]
[singing along] ♪
Lama nama
doo a nama nama nama seema lama
♪
Lama nama seema nama
doo ma nama hama, yeah
♪♪
-[♪ Tevin Campbell sings "Can We Talk?"]
-[singing along] ♪
Can we talk
♪
for a minute?
Whoo!
♪
Girl, I want to know your name
♪♪
-[♪ Boyz II Men sing "End of the Road"]
-[singing along] ♪
Although we've come
♪
to the end of the road
still, I can't let go
♪
It's unnatural
You belong to me
♪
I belong to you
Come to the end of the road
♪♪
-Did you ever see the original
Twister?
-[groans]
Great movie.
-[groans] Why?
-Well, first off,
the special effects.
But also Bill Paxton? Helen Hunt?
Their smoking on-screen chemistry,
which was...
Mwah!
'Cause tornados are dope. [laughs]
[ringtone plays]
Have you talked to Ayden yet?
No. I need to have the conversation,
but I'm nervous.
Mama, you have to trust, okay?
You got to put this in His hands.
[chuckles] Capital "H," like God.
Oh, really? I don't remember
seeing you in church for a while.
I'm going this Sunday.
It's new, but I figured I got to start
putting my money where my mouth is
instead of my mouth where his money is.
You know what I mean?
Oh. Okay. Well, good for you.
Making changes is hard,
and you're taking this seriously.
-I see you.
-I mean, switching it up
has got to be better than staying stuck
in this bad pattern,
'cause if I don't change
how I'm dating, at this rate,
Jesus will come again,
and I will still be single.
Girl, we can't have you single
at the Rapture.
May He bless my swipe, because
I'm 'bout to go Bible on these boys!
♪
Jesus
♪♪
[laughing]
-Okay, I love you.
-I love you, too, honey.
Good luck.
-[phone beeps]
-[chuckles]
[sighs] And good luck to me.
[gentle music playing]
You only hate the story
because you're all down with love.
Because you're the poster boy
for relationships?
-I'm not against them.
-I'm not, either.
I just have a list
of what I'm looking for in a guy.
Of course you do.
And I'm not gonna settle
for anything less.
I would love to see that list.
I'm sure you would.
-Hit me.
-Okay.
At least six feet, no more than six-four.
Cutting out tons of guys
for a superficial reason.
That's great.
Doesn't work in my industry.
Where you spend
the majority of your waking hours.
Parents still married.
Fifty percent of marriages end in divorce.
Congratulations,
you just eliminated half the population.
This list is doing nothing
but keeping you single.
You do know that real love
isn't subject to a list?
Values family.
Now, that I got to give you.
-I want what my parents have.
-[Bluetooth chimes]
[automated voice]
Text from
Candice dancing girl in a red dress emoji.
Read text?
-No! No!
-Yes! Absolutely!
[Jarrett] Disconnect. Thank you.
"Thinking about you, big daddy."
Do you want to reply?
-No! Discontinue!
-[laughing]
Disconnect!
[lighthearted music playing]
-Don't leave her hanging, big daddy.
-Please.
Really? Really?
-I-I haven't spoke to her in ages.
-Mm.
She texted me out of nowhere.
How many people are you
"intentionally dating" right now?
-Relationship Goals
says...
-Oh, God.
...date away,
-as long as you do it with purpose.
-[sighs] Mm.
I want my next relationship to be my wife.
Okay, big daddy.
[Leah laughing]
You said you wanted
what your parents have.
Yeah.
How long have they been married now?
Fifty years and counting.
Impressive.
I, uh, heard about your mom.
I've been wanting to tell you
how sorry I am.
I know how close you were.
Thanks.
But I'm fine.
Are you, though?
Hi there. What can I get y'all?
-Oh. Well, um...
-Um...
I'll have the, uh, Caesar salad, please.
Sure thing.
-Uh...
-Mm-hmm?
-Doris, is it?
-Yes.
-Doris, um...
-Mm-hmm.
Do you know if
the, uh, fish is farm-raised?
Well, yes.
You see, Dennis the trout grew up on
a farm with his six brothers and sisters,
where they rode horses
and swam in the stream,
until one day he was caught in a net
and then filleted by a six-inch blade
and thrown on a broiler.
You know, now Dennis is just waiting
for some smooth guy
to ask him where he grew up
and what's his pedigree
so he can decide if Dennis is good enough
to grace his plate.
-I will have the trout.
-Good.
-And, um--
-You don't get any more questions.
[laughing]
Did that just happen?
Okay. You sure you can do this?
I was once told that I have
a natural talent for improv.
Okay. By whom?
-Irrelevant.
-Oh, my God, let's go.
-[door closes]
-[♪ Amores de Mentira sing "Guaguancó"]
-Hi, everyone! Ah!
¡Mami!
-[lively chatter]
-You look so beautiful. Mwah.
-Mwah.
Um, I want to introduce you all
to my boyfriend Roland.
[Roland] Greetings, all.
[Treese] It's-it's really new, but, um,
I have been really intentional
about my dating, and it's...
it's getting pretty serious.
[mispronounces]
Química instantánea.
[laughs]
¡Bienvenido!
Oh.
-Muchas gracias.
-De nada.
Oh, ¿qué haces?
[basketball game playing over TV]
-Teresa, honey?
-Mm-hmm?
-Come help me in the dining room.
-Yeah.
You can give it up, honey,
'cause you know good and well
that man is not your boyfriend.
What? Yes, he is.
That's my boyfriend. We're dating.
You are not dating him.
What's going on with you?
You're spiraling.
Is it because your cousin Daniela
is younger than you
and she has that hot boyfriend
who makes all that coin?
[Treese]
Oh, my God
.
Maybe I'm just tired of you guys
thinking that something is wrong with me
just 'cause I'm single.
Hey, now, we're only
looking at you sideways
because you brought a fake boyfriend
to Sunday supper.
Maybe I think something's wrong with me
because I'm still single.
Baby, there's nothing wrong with you.
And it's okay to be sad if you are.
Men love tears.
It's true.
Makes them feel all macho and strong.
Oh, my God.
Who do you suggest I seduce
with my sadness? Tío Juan?
Not a bad idea.
That is really problematic
-and really nasty.
-[laughs]
Whatever. He's not a blood relative.
-Mom.
-What?
[lighthearted music playing]
-[whispering] Stop.
-[mouthing]
[♪ Mare sings "Peace of Mind"]
♪
Turning up the volume on the silence
Still, it's hard to sleep...
Oh, uh, what-what...
what you doing over there?
-Take a break. You don't need-- Gimme.
-[scoffs]
You don't need this book. We are goals.
-Oh, really?
-Mm-hmm.
Why? Because people think
we're a power couple?
Because we get millions of likes
on Instagram?
Because we got sponsored by
those power bars?
No doubt. We like Jay and Bey,
minus the
Lemonade.
-We keep it Perrier.
-That's true.
Yeah, yeah. But not just that.
We love each other, okay?
-You are my strong...
-Mm.
...smart, beautiful powerhouse
of a girlfriend.
For four years now.
Mm, we said we weren't in a rush.
No, you said that, and I pretended
to agree, and that's my bad.
-[whispering] Ow.
-Okay? That's me being real.
-I'm being accountable.
-Mm-hmm.
But now I'm saying something else, baby.
We're either doing God's will
or we're not.
Well, how do you know His will isn't this?
This? Us living together,
sleeping together, eating together?
We share a cell phone plan.
Two lines, one bill--
that sounds like convenience to me.
-Okay. Yes. Hear me out.
-Mm-hmm.
Look what he says.
"Dating isn't just playtime.
It isn't pretending you're married.
It isn't treating a season
like a lifetime."
[Ayden sighs]
This is a fake marriage
with everything but the covenant.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold up.
What we have is not fake.
My love for you is real, okay?
But if we're talking about seasons,
let me just get through this one first,
and then I'll have the headspace
to figure out you and me.
I love you, Ayden,
but I need us to make a decision.
I've been acting like your wife,
but I'm only your girlfriend.
So I'm gonna stop acting like your wife.
I don't get it. What does that mean?
I mean that until we can figure out
where this is going,
I'm gonna go stay at Treese's.
-What? Come on.
-Yeah.
I'm not gonna be your plus-one.
And... [sighs]
I'm gonna have to take sex off the table.
-All-all-all the kinds?
-That's what you heard?
All the words I said,
and that's what you heard?
[doorbell buzzes]
[Treese] Coming.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Got room on the couch?
Come here.
[clicks tongue]
I did it.
[♪ Mighty Pen and Johnny Wood
sing "Imagine"]
♪
Can you imagine
what it would be like
♪
if they never told you
what it should be like...
Now I can say, without a doubt,
that there's nothing worse
than being stuck in a car for six hours
with Jarrett Roy.
Oh, okay. What did you two talk about?
The fact that you have,
like, crazy chemistry?
-We do not.
-Really?
So, Team Denial has entered
the group chat. Word.
Okay, Brenda, back me up here, please.
Um--
Brenda? You okay?
Ayden didn't react well
to Project Put a Ring on It.
No, but I'm staying the course,
even if it means the end of me and Ayden.
Look, I got something for you, okay?
"Trust in the Lord with all your heart.
Seek His will in all you do,
and He will show you which path to take."
Amen.
Did I just microdose?
On Jesus.
[Leah sighs]
[Michael]
Dating around
might be fun for a season,
but I promise you,
-it will leave you feeling empty.
-[Leah sighs]
This isn't working for me.
It's a glorified puff piece.
And you want to make it a takedown.
No, but if you had it your way,
this story would be about an inch deep.
It's a feel-good story,
not a
Dateline
undercover investigation.
But it's no angle, only fandom.
You won't get into anything meaningful,
so it's just glossy drivel.
Yes.
-It should be gritty.
-Mm.
The mark of all
great Valentine's Day stories.
-[♪ Doechii sings "Denial Is a River"]
-♪
What's up, Doechii...
No one wants to take advice from someone
preaching perfection from a soapbox.
You want to sell hope?
Fine, but the story
has got to be real, too.
It does not have to be cynical to be real.
Look.
"Embrace the season you're in.
Thank God for it."
See? That's the vibe.
Positive, upbeat, hopeful.
♪
Uh, uh, uh, uh, ah
Woosah
♪♪
[Leah sighs] We want to do our own cuts.
You can choose which one is better.
Spoken like a true team player.
We're just not seeing eye to eye.
The assignment was to work together.
That one.
Valentine's Day is two weeks away.
If you two can't cooperate
and get it done on time,
maybe neither of you
is fit to run this show.
-I can do it.
-It's not a problem.
Magic. You see how quickly
that was settled?
-[♪ Saweetie and Jhené Aiko sing
"Back to the Streets"]
-♪
Pull up in my hood, best dressed...
[Jarrett]
There wouldn't be a story unless
I presented one.
Why aren't you listening?
This is morning television,
not prime time.
Okay, I'm getting real tired of you
questioning my ability...
♪
on a leash
Traded in my old ...
♪
He was just a lease,
I ride around town till I leave...
[gasps] Okay.
He is fine.
Wow, look at his muscles.
No.
Fix your aim.
-Chip?
-Yeah.
They're wet 'cause I cried on them.
♪
Best dressed, next thing, upgrade
-♪
Who's next?
♪
-♪
Who's next?
♪
Rich boy, got him on deck...
So, we should stay on Michael here,
and then pull back to show--
Natalie's reaction in a two-shot.
-Look at us, finishing each other's--
-I will not.
[singsongy] You know you want to.
It's called dating intentionally.
You get to know each other for 90 days.
Good luck with that.
No pressure. [chuckles]
No sex.
Cool. That's a no from me.
And decide if you want
to keep seeing each other.
Yes. I'm all about soul ties
and high-frequency love vibrations.
Oh, my-- Yes. Right?
Which is why polyamory is my path.
Oh.
Will you go on this journey with us,
-my earth angel?
-[snickers]
[whispers] I don't think so.
-[girl 1] Open.
-[whistle blows]
-[shoes squeaking]
-[girl 2] Again.
[girl 3] Pass it.
-[whistle blows]
-[girl 4] You guys want to do it again?
-[girl 5] Yeah.
-[Papa Jim] Okay. Keep it moving.
-Keep it moving.
-[Leah] Team is looking good.
Certainly looking better
than they did last year.
[laughing]
-What about you?
-Mm, I'm good.
Just keeping my head down
and fighting for this job.
[sighs] I love you, baby girl,
and I appreciate your hustle,
but this title is not your whole identity.
I'm worried that
that's all you see anymore.
I mean, what is success if you don't have
someone you love to share it with?
Okay, Mr. Billy Dee.
I know you're trying to look out for me,
but not everyone needs that.
Everyone needs love and connection.
Yeah, well, look what happened to Mom.
We loved her with our whole hearts,
and she got cancer and died.
Loss is a part of life.
If you try to avoid it...
...you miss out on all the good stuff.
[wistful music playing]
Look.
Your mother and I shared
something beautiful,
and I want that for you.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[bag zips]
-Hey.
How are you doing?
I've definitely been better. You?
Same. [clears throat]
Have you thought about things?
I got to be honest.
Okay? Um...
I'm just really stressed out
about retiring
and becoming some has-been
talking head on TV, okay?
It-It's just a lot of pressure on me
right now, babe, okay?
Yes, and I know the timing is not good,
but I can't keep pushing down how I feel.
We had a good thing going,
and then you pick up this damn book?
I've been letting my faith and my needs
take a back seat in this relationship
because I love you,
but I can't keep doing that.
[Brenda's breath trembling]
I can't keep going down this path
that's making me sacrifice
who I am, what I want and what I believe.
And if you really love me the way you say
you would, you would make that commitment.
[melancholy music playing]
This clearly isn't moving
towards marriage.
So it's over, Ayden.
[crying softly] It's over.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[voice breaking] The fact is,
Ayden doesn't want me.
He doesn't want to marry me.
Then he's a complete idiot, obviously.
I mean, he is a pro baller.
That we hope gets it together, right?
But in the event that he doesn't, are we
gonna be buying voodoo dolls on Etsy?
[Brenda scoffs]
What we're definitely doing
is standing by our friend,
who's the best, and you deserve the world.
Yeah.
-Listen, I know this sucks.
-Yeah.
-But we love you.
-So much.
-And we're here for you.
-Mm-hmm.
Thank you. I love you guys, too.
I just wish it didn't hurt so bad.
-I know.
-Voodoo dolls, definitely.
-[laughs, sniffles]
-[whispers] For sure.
You know what, I just can't believe
that after all this time,
I wasted four years at my age,
and now I have to start all over.
-Girl, please calm down.
-What? Shut-- No!
-Yeah.
-Are you kidding me?
-You are in your prime.
You got carded last week.
[woman] Oh, my God. No way.
-Can I get a picture with you after class?
-[Brenda laughs]
My grandma loves your show.
-What? No.
-Go.
[Treese] You know what?
We are going out tonight.
We are going clubbing.
We're gonna cheer you up, and we're
gonna get a voodoo doll for that heifer.
-Absolutely.
-[laughs]
Is this not the spot anymore?
Last time we came through, it was poppin'.
Last time when, like a decade ago?
Ladies, it's only 9:00.
Oh, well, thank you so much
for your input.
We have work in the morning.
What, no one's trying to get lit
at a reasonable hour anymore?
-Stop. You are making it worse.
-Just saying.
But we're here.
So, come on, girls.
-One song.
-[grunts excitedly]
-I like that.
-Let's go!
-[♪ Ciara sings "Goodies"]
-♪
My goodies, my goodies
♪
[singing along] ♪
my goodies,
not my goodies, ow
♪
You may look at me and think
that I'm just a young girl
♪
but I'm not just a young girl
-[laughs]
-♪
Baby, this is what I'm looking for
♪
-♪
I bet you want the goodies
Bet you thought about it
♪
-♪
Yeah
♪
-♪
Got you all hot and bothered
mad 'cause I talk around it
♪
-[laughing]
If you're looking for the goodies,
keep on looking
♪
'cause they stay in the jar
Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, yeah
♪
-♪
You may talk slick, trying to hit...
-Oh, oh, oh, oh!
-Malfunction! Malfunction.
-Okay, now--
[all exclaiming]
-[laughing]
-♪
It's just how I gotta have it
♪
-♪
I bet you want the goodies
♪
-♪
Ah
♪
Bet you thought about it
If you're looking for the goodies,
keep on looking
♪
'cause they stay in the jar
-♪
Oh-oh, oh-oh
♪
-[whooping]
-Yeah!
-♪
oh-oh, oh-oh, yeah
♪
If you're looking for the goodies,
keep on looking
♪
-[laughing]
-♪
'cause they stay in the jar
♪♪
-Come on, Brenda. Brenda!
-[grunting]
Brenda, Brenda, Brenda, Brenda, Brenda!
-Oh. [laughing]
-Oh, my God.
May we never be in a club
with people again.
Thank you, ladies. I needed this.
-Of course.
-[sighs]
-So you guys ready to bounce?
-Yes.
-Absolutely. Thought you'd never ask.
-Let's go. Let's go.
[horns honking]
[sighs]
Hey, uh, I just saw the cut.
Sorry, I'm not feeling it.
[Leah] I-- Me, neither. I have some notes.
And I bet your notes
are the exact opposite of mine.
[sighs] My notes are right.
I don't know where that leaves yours,
but I can't help it if, you know--
You're on the right side of history.
Yeah, we get it.
Okay, you guys, look.
We've done 20 cuts, and
all you guys have done so far is bicker.
And I say that with all due respect.
So, why don't you give me both sets
of your notes, go into the break room,
I'll take another pass,
and I'll let you know when I'm done.
[lighthearted music playing]
Thank you.
[Jarrett sighs]
-[Leah] Thank you, Quentin.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
Ay-yi-yi.
-[yawning] Kobe.
-I saw that.
Morning TV's a beast. Can't hack it?
Please. You wish I wasn't Jarrett Roy,
legendary king of the grind.
You wish you were a legendary anything.
[laughs, clicks tongue]
Uh, are you trying to make my eyes bleed?
What's wrong with winking?
Nothing, as long as you're sneezing
or having a seizure.
[laughing] Okay, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
So people who have seizures
get a loophole?
Oh, Le-Le. Ah.
Reminds me of when we were starting out.
What, assistants burning the midnight oil?
No. You always having lists and rules.
Well, I can't help it
if I know how things should be.
You know what?
That is an interesting rebrand of
"doesn't play well with others."
-Don't you think?
-Well, it's better than
"all he wants to do is play with others."
That's fair.
But that was then.
People change, grow up,
figure out what or who...
...is worth investing their time in.
-Is it hot in here?
-Nah.
Everything feels perfect to me.
[laughs] Okay. Really?
[♪ Little Monarch sings "Strike"]
[Leah laughing]
♪
Who are you gonna be
when you step outside?
♪
You gotta make...
[laughs] Yes! I win again!
Mm.
♪
be when you step outside?
You gotta make that lightning strike
♪♪
[mouth full] Mmm. Mmm, pretty good.
Pretty good. Mmm. Mmm.
[♪ The Doobie Brothers sing
"What a Fool Believes"]
[Jarrett singing along]
♪
He's watching her go
But what a fool believes
♪
he sees
No wise man has the power
♪
[Leah] Whoo!
to reason away
♪
What seems
to be
♪
-Guys?
-♪
is always better than nothing
♪
-Nothing, baby. Uh-huh. Come on, now.
-Nothing, nothing!
-Guys. Guys.
-♪
than nothing at all
♪♪
[music stops]
I'm sorry for the interruption,
but, um, the piece is finished.
Oh, piece is finished. Nice.
Yes.
[lighthearted music playing]
-We will never speak of this again.
-You got it.
But the image of you
playing that air piano
will live rent-free in my head forever.
[laughs] I was good, right?
It means shifting your focus
from the superficial.
This is...
This is... [sighs]
good.
Really good.
Well done, Quentin.
Thanks.
[stammers] I used both sets of your notes
and made them work together.
To be honest,
they were pretty complementary.
Oh.
-Um, yeah, well...
-[clears throat]
Cool. That's, um, great.
-Great.
-Yeah, thanks, Quentin.
Uh, send us the link,
and we'll get this right over to Dan.
You got it.
[lighthearted music playing]
Happy Singles Awareness Day.
[laughs] Thanks.
But you know
I don't eat anything heart-shaped.
-[chuckles]
-I got you something, too.
For Valentine's Day?
No.
To commemorate us finding a way
to work together and finish the story.
Are you sure there's no anthrax in there?
I'd go with a pipe bomb.
-More dramatic!
-Yeah, you would.
-[chuckles]
-[Leah laughing]
Okay.
-A monument to my finest moment.
-Mm.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm touched.
[♪ Victoria Monét and Bryson Tiller sing
"We Might Even Be Falling in Love"]
Happy Valentine's Day.
[scoffs] Is it, Ted?
Is it? What's so happy about today, huh?
Who's happy?
[chuckling]
If you don't like Valentine's Day,
how about Happy Galen--
[groans] Now, I know you are not about
to say that word to me right now, Ted,
unless you want a self-tanning accident.
Do you want to look like a pumpkin
on national TV today, Ted?
♪
Ooh
Love, love, love
♪
Ooh...
[Roland clears throat]
♪
Go, go, go 'head...
Thanks.
♪
Freestyle with me
till you find your groove in it
♪
Oh, we might let me move in it
Said you ain't had nobody
hit it like you did...
This Valentine's Day, we're looking
at love through a different lens
and exploring what role faith can play
in our personal lives.
[Ted] Now, let me tell you, Brenda,
this story brought up a lot for me
and, as you know, sparked
a vigorous debate amongst our staff.
[chuckles] It did.
And now we went to Tulsa, Oklahoma,
to speak with someone
who has a lot to say on the topic.
-Let's take a look.
-[graphic whooshes]
Whether it's at his church, on YouTube,
or in the pages of
his
New York Times
best-selling book,
Michael Todd is changing lives
and bringing hope
to people all over the country.
So, why did you name your book
Relationship Goals?
Well, I wanted to take a trendy hashtag
that pop culture has basically defined,
and I wanted to point it to something
bigger than ourselves: our faith.
The thing that all of us need to actually
see and reach our relationship goals.
When you talk about a trendy hashtag,
-that's exactly what it is, right?
-Yeah.
-"Hashtag relationship goals!"
But it's like, just 'cause you held hands
on the top of a mountain
doesn't mean you're
the perfect couple, right?
-Right, right.
-No. It's something way deeper than that.
And it takes work.
[Brenda]
We spoke with some people
who turned to the book
for help with their love lives.
My life was wild
before I came across
Relationship Goals.
I was dating whoever I wanted to.
I was drinking, smoking, really just lost.
[Michael]
Dating around
might be fun for a season,
but I promise you
it will leave you feeling empty.
-Do you walk the talk?
-[Natalie] We do.
We did make some--
well, Mike made a few mistakes
-early on.
-[laughter]
I don't know about me, but, uh...
Sorry, big guy.
I was afraid of commitment,
and I wasn't fully honest with her.
I didn't tell her everything that I was
dealing with, the fear that I had.
I was addicted to all kinds of things,
liar, manipulator,
addicted to pornography.
I had secrets,
so I lost her.
You had to be willing
to let the love of your life go
in order to get what you needed
-in a relationship.
-[Natalie]
Yes.
-So many ways. [chuckles]
-Our marriage has benefited
in so many ways,
even from very practical things,
from just simple communication.
Just not relationship with one another
but also the relationship
that we're building with our kids.
[Magaly Lares]
My biggest takeaway
from
Relationship Goals
is to learn to love yourself,
embrace all the details of you.
[Michael]
It means shifting your focus
from the superficial.
This is why I wrote this book,
to be able to help people understand.
-We broke up.
-[Natalie]
Yep.
[Michael]
But then we refocused,
and we realigned our aim.
And we came back together.
[Brenda] Wow.
A sweet message
on the sweetest day of the year.
We'll be right back.
[gentle music playing]
I got good news, my people!
Early numbers have come in,
and ratings are the highest
for any Valentine's segment we've run.
[cheering]
-Yes! We did it!
-Yes! Whoo!
This is so amazing, Jarrett.
We smoked the other shows, too.
[Dan chuckles] Nothing but ashes.
Just how I like it.
I know Leah wanted you to go out
with the win you were looking for.
-[Roland grunts playfully]
-I'm glad we delivered.
Credit where credit is due.
This was your idea, Jarrett,
and it's a big hit.
The piece wouldn't have been anywhere
near as good without Leah pushing us
to create a well-rounded, impactful story.
Well, the results are undeniable.
Thank you, Leah, for getting on board.
The network has a very tough decision
at the end of this month.
You two are extremely strong candidates.
And I have to say,
you bring out the best in each other.
[Leah]
"This story hit so hard.
I Amazon'd a copy
of
Relationship Goals
right away."
"I've been having a rough time,
one guy dogging me out after the next."
-[Leah] Mm.
-"I finally have hope
that I can break the pattern."
Fluff doesn't have the power
to do that, does it?
Have you seen these comments?
Our socials are blowing up.
So, uh, you going
on the victory tour without me?
-[laughing]
-[laughing] Le-Le.
[Jarrett and Leah continue laughing]
Okay, I'm going to--
[groaning] Ah! Ah! Oh.
My leg fell asleep
at the worst possible time.
Traitor!
Pretend I'm not here.
[grunts]
Why, leg, why?
-Pins and needles.
-[feet stomping]
Pins and needles. Ooh.
Your story really struck a chord.
Our story.
And in the spirit of mutual success,
what do you say we take the night off
from being mortal enemies to celebrate?
A ceasefire?
-One condition.
-Name it.
We go back to hating each other tomorrow.
[♪ Amber Mark sings "Let Me Love You"]
That goes without saying.
[both laughing]
♪
Not stopping this
way that I feel
♪
I might wanna strip
Hey.
♪
I taste so good...
Wow. Stunning.
You also look... good.
Nice fit.
Roy, party of two.
-[chuckles] Wow.
-Yeah. Yeah.
This place is so dope.
Cool, right?
Thank you.
I mean, I thought I knew
every secret spot in this city, but...
I'm impressed.
I ain't hear that.
What'd you say, now? Huh?
You know you heard me.
-I did. My fault.
-[laughs]
[♪ TARANEH sings "Keep Up"]
-[Leah] Mm.
-[Jarrett] Look at that.
[gasps] Thank you.
-[Jarrett purring]
-Come on.
-You really went with a cosmo?
-Mm-hmm.
-Here?
Where everyone is deeply cool
in a way that would be threatening
if I wasn't looking so fly tonight?
-Oh, one, you do look fly tonight.
-Mm.
Two, I don't really care much
what most people think,
but I do care what you think.
You got under my skin like a splinter
from the first time we met.
Really?
Really.
[inhales sharply]
The way you react the most
when you're excited.
How you'd do anything
for the people you care about.
Hell, you even challenge me
to be better at my job
and just better in general. Yeah.
You're sophisticated, funny, smart
and, Lord knows,
as tenacious as a cockroach.
-A cockroach?
-Yeah, cockroach.
-La cucaracha.
-[laughing]
Tu es tout ce que je veux.
You learned French for me.
Uh, ChatGPT, but it still counts, right?
-[Leah laughing]
-Hmm?
-Still counts.
-Mm.
-It means...
-[sighs]
...you're everything I want.
All this time, I wondered what we could
have had if I hadn't screwed things up.
You're not just everything I want, Leah.
[softly] Come here.
You are...
...everything.
You're not gonna wink at me, are you?
I'm most definitely not going to wink.
♪
Baby, keep up with me
♪♪
-[♪ Sidibe, Devin Morrison and Herb Alpert
sing "Ready Enough"]
-♪
All I gotta do is be here now
♪
-[laughing]
-♪
Why did it take so long
♪
to figure out?
Let love define you
♪
-[laughing]
-♪
Everything that I've been
♪
looking for
is waiting for a chance to be
♪
I'm ready enough
I'm already love
♪♪
[gasps]
[lighthearted music playing]
[books clattering]
Oh. Morning.
Are you sneaking out?
Yes. This was a huge mistake!
Okay, don't do this, Leah. Don't run.
You're scared and you're shutting down.
Don't do it.
-You and I could have something real.
-Because you've changed?
No one changes,
not at the core of who they are.
I'm not the man that I was back then.
We drank too much,
and this never should have happened.
You can't say that.
Why? What chapter is this in the book?
Okay, I hear you,
-but let's talk about it.
-[sighs]
No. [groans]
[sighs] And put those away.
My abs?
Yes. So manipulative.
Unfair business practice.
Here.
-You might need this.
-Thank you.
Can't we just speak about this like adul--
-Goodbye, Jarrett.
-Bye?
Wait, what?
That's it?
Really?
You know what? Fine.
You can get all bent out of shape.
You can run out of here
and say this shouldn't have happened.
But it did.
And what-what are you gonna do,
ignore me forever?
We work together, remember?
Not for long.
I'm...
gonna be showrunner.
I don't know
how I could be so stupid, again!
This...
was the biggest mistake of my life.
[Jarrett] Leah.
Leah. Look, don't--
[door closes]
[melancholy music playing]
Best night of mine.
-[siren wailing in distance]
-[horn honks]
-So, do you have feelings for him?
-Yes.
-Anger.
-Oh.
Disdain, disgust, annoyance.
Any of the fun kind?
-I'm so mad at myself.
-[laughs]
[Ayden] Brenda!
Hold up.
Get your voodoo dolls ready, ladies.
Okay. All right, relax.
I'm only here to talk.
Obviously. What else are you gonna do,
braid her hair?
Count the pigeons?
Guess what, there are none.
You can leave now, okay?
It's all right. I'll hear him out.
-Are you sure?
-Because I will fight this fool.
[Brenda] I know. Just give me a minute.
You guys, go ahead. I'll be right in.
Don't start none, won't be none.
Okay, okay. I deserve that.
[Ayden chuckles]
[sighs]
I miss you, Brenda.
I can't sleep. I can't eat.
I can't even play.
That's what this is about?
Basketball? [scoffs]
-As God is my witness, Ayden, I cannot--
-No.
It's not that.
Okay, it's...
Anything good doesn't feel good
if you're not there, too.
All right?
I don't want to do life without you, baby.
I took some notes.
"Our separation was a mistake.
I want to try again,
with God in our relationship this time."
You read my book?
Yeah, cover to cover.
I underlined some things, too.
[both laugh]
Look, I know that you're angry,
and I'm sure you have your doubts,
but tonight's my retirement party,
and I'd really love it
if you'd come celebrate with me.
-You said this wasn't about basketball.
-It's not.
It's about trying to get back
to the way things were.
So, please come tonight.
[sentimental music playing]
[sighs]
[elevator bell dings]
I don't know. I think if Ayden is
asking for another chance,
he might be ready to step up.
Or maybe he's going to string
Brenda along some more.
Okay, well, she won't know
unless she goes.
Does Brenda have a say in this?
Look, I just think that sometimes
you have to show up to things. Hint, hint.
Oh. My dad got to you, too?
Yeah, we're on a family group chat.
[chuckles]
-[♪ Leon Thomas sings "MUTT"]
-♪
She said, "Take your time
♪
What's the rush?"
[lively chatter]
♪
I said, "Baby, I'm a dog, I'm a mutt"
She said, "Take your time,
what's the rush?"
♪
-♪
Oh
♪
-[indistinct chatter]
I said, "Baby, I'm a dog, I'm a mutt..."
Uh... are you sure about this?
No, but I'm here. [sighs]
Thanks.
And so is your revenge bod.
You look amazing.
-Mm-hmm.
-Thank you.
♪ ♪
-Hey, beautiful. How are you?
-Hi.
You look so good.
Hold this for a second? Thank you.
-Come here, baby.
-Why? What?
-Come here. Come here. Come here.
-[laughs] What are you doing?
-[music stops]
-[guests murmuring]
[chuckles]
Brenda Phelps,
every moment that I spend with you
is a blessing.
And if there's one thing I'm sure of,
it's that spending
the rest of my life with you
would mean that I'd always be winning.
-[guests murmuring]
-So...
[sobs]
[guests exclaiming]
[Ayden chuckles]
That better not be a championship ring.
[sentimental music playing]
-You and me under God, baby.
-[sobs]
Would you make me
the happiest man in the world
and do me the honor of being my wife?
[crying] Yes, of course.
I love you, Ayden Young.
[guests cheering]
[crying]
-No, other one.
-Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
Yeah. We got to do it right.
[laughing]
[sighs] I'm so sorry
that it took me this long
to realize that
I couldn't live without you.
You're perfect.
-I love you.
[guests whooping, shouting]
-[♪ Aiza and Trevor M. Simpson sing
"I'm in Love"]
-♪
We danced on the moon...
[Treese exclaims, laughs]
-[Ayden] Yes, yes, yes!
-[excited chatter]
[both laughing]
♪
Blowing up like I should
Shining like Hollywood
♪
-♪
I think I'm in love
♪♪
-[phone ringing]
Leah Caldwell's office. Roland speaking.
Hey.
[murmurs excitedly]
Dan wants to see you.
Do you think this is it?
They were supposed to make a decision
next week, but do you think they did it?
I'm panicking.
You need to find your inner peace.
[inhales sharply]
[exhales slowly]
[stomach grumbles]
M-My inner peace wants a bagel.
Why are you still sitting down, woman?
-Let's go!
-Okay, okay! I'm coming, I'm coming!
I won't bury the lede. The job is yours.
[stammers] Show-Showrunner?
I'm showrunner?
-Yes!
-Oh, my God!
-Thank you!
-[laughing]
-Showrunner! Come on.
-Thank you, Dan.
Oh, my gosh!
I am so sorry the network put you
through the wringer. [grunts]
But I got to say, I couldn't be prouder
to hand over the reins of the show
to somebody who's as dedicated
and talented as you.
Thank you.
Not to mention a team player.
Should we get you a jersey?
As long as it says "number one."
-Yeah!
-[both laugh]
Does Jarrett know?
Actually, he took himself
out of the running.
[busy chatter]
You said you wanted this job and you were
going to go after it, no holds barred.
And you said if I was really sorry,
I would drop out of the running, right?
I wasn't serious.
I was calling your bluff.
Well, now I'm calling yours.
There's only one person
who should run this show.
I thought I was here for the job...
...but I'm thinking I was put here
for a different purpose.
And you were right.
I should've never tried
to take this from you.
[gentle music playing]
-Yeah.
-[Leah speaking indistinctly]
[Roland exclaims]
[group] Congratulations!
-[excited chatter, laughter]
-[upbeat pop music playing]
To our newly crowned boss.
The best lady boss in the biz.
The best boss, period, Ted.
Okay?
-Sorry, Treese. Absolutely correct.
-Okay.
You scare me, and I like it.
However bittersweet it is to leave a place
that's been such a huge part of my life,
I must say, I do step away to learn
my grandkids' names with confidence...
-[laughter]
-...because
I know truly that you are all
in the very best hands.
To Leah.
-[group] Leah.
-And to Dan.
-And to Dan. Come on.
-No. No.
-Yeah! Whoo!
-[excited chatter]
-Yeah.
-All right, now, take a lid off.
Take a lid off.
-[Brenda] Congratulations!
-[upbeat R&B music playing]
[laughter]
Girl, you did exactly
what you set out to do, huh?
Yeah! Are you so excited?
I am.
But I... I have to admit,
it doesn't feel like much of a win
since Jarrett forfeited.
Girl, he quit because
you deserved the job.
And now you're just gonna let him
ride off into the sunset?
You know what?
We never have to talk about
Jarrett Roy again.
-So, cheers to that.
-Period.
-Okay.
-And to Brenda, our beautiful bride.
And to me, your sad-sack,
perma-single friend!
No, no, I did not sign off
on toasting to that.
No, this is, this is actually
really good, you know?
I'm-I'm excited.
I... I don't need a man right now.
I was trying to date a little differently,
but I realize I missed
a really important step.
My season of single.
-Aw.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Well, even if you're single,
you are never alone.
You've got us.
Mm. I love you guys.
-We love you back.
-[chuckles]
-We would never ghost you.
-Yes.
-I didn't mean to bring that up.
-Damn, girl.
That was bad timing. Yeah.
-[♪ Kelly Rowland and Method Man
sing "Complicated"]
-♪
Been a couple months
♪
and I been feeling feelings,
but don't wanna jump the gun
♪
'cause I don't wanna assess the vibes
But I'm easy, right? That's a lie
♪
I been dying just to make you mine,
but, bae, give me a sign
♪
Games are freaking lame...
[Ayden] This is the one, huh?
-[Brenda] This one, this one.
-[Ayden] Okay. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
-Okay, you got it, you got it.
-Uh-oh. Got it?
Okay, this is a big piece.
-Boom. You got it?
-Mmm.
-So good.
-Yeah?
-[Brenda] Oh.
-[chuckles]
[Treese's mom] You got
yourself a boyfriend.
[playfully] And he's so cute.
-Aw. Honey.
-[dog whimpers]
Hi, Boyfriend.
♪
Why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪♪
-[birds chirping]
-[wind whistling softly]
[wistful music playing]
[sniffles]
[clears throat]
[sighs]
[crying] Mom.
I need you.
I need you to tell me...
[sobbing]
I need you to tell me
why I got everything I wanted
and I'm still not happy.
[crying]
-Daddy.
-[sighs]
I miss her so much.
[Papa Jim] I see her in you every day.
She'd be so proud of you.
[Michael over TV]
...that a woman needs
to actually be vulnerable.
-[Natalie]
That's right.
-[Michael]
So it's a perfect storm.
That's why I tell people all the time
they need to do the emotional work.
Actually get with somebody
that can help you unpack,
'cause then you can pack
for a trip with somebody
and go somewhere you've never gone before.
But until you unpack, you can't repack.
That's the truth of all relationships.
[softly] He's right.
[lighthearted music playing]
Hey.
-Hey.
-Hi.
So...
I think I love Jarrett.
-Finally!
-Yeah, we know.
You knew?
Girl, we are your best friends.
Yeah, we saw how you two
look at each other.
-Plus his slammin' dental hygiene.
-Mm.
I didn't think I needed to fix my aim,
but you were right.
I needed to rip up my list
and open my heart.
So you could find love.
But what do I do, though? Jarrett left.
Girl, after you refused to talk to him.
And he gave up his dream job for you.
Hello?
So you think he might feel
the same way about me?
-Did you get hit with a stupid stick?
-Yes, girl.
[Roland] But he's moving to L.A.
It's so tragic.
[grunts]
[Treese] Spill.
I will be kicked out of the assistants'
inner circle of secrets and gossip.
Okay, I heard Jarrett took a job
running Audible's West Coast office.
-That's it. It's over.
-What?
Have you never seen a rom-com?
Girl, this is where you fight
for your man, okay?
You... you got to make a grand gesture.
Yes! We stan this matchup.
What am I supposed to do, though?
Jarrett's moving across the country.
-Then you have to tell him how you feel.
-[Treese] And fast.
Right? You got to run!
Why can't I call him like a normal person?
Or send a nice text?
Maybe slide into his DMs?
-No.
-Are you nuts?
Texting seems fine to me.
You are so young.
I know rom-coms, okay?
-You got to run!
-Plus there's no time.
Jarrett's on the 3:45 Delta flight
to L.A. today.
How do you know that?
Assistants' inner circle
of secrets and gossip.
-It's a sacred space.
-You got to get to the airport!
[Treese and Roland] Run!
I can't literally run to JFK.
[energetic music playing]
Excuse me. Um, I saw that guy
put something super sus in his bag.
-Which one?
-The one with the checkered hoodie.
[lighthearted music playing]
Yep.
Excuse me, sir. Come with us.
Sir, out of line.
We just have a couple questions.
Mm.
[busy chatter]
[door closes]
You did this?
I'm sorry.
I had to stop you.
What are you playing at, Leah, hmm?
I got a flight to catch.
You know how I hate you?
Okay, this is starting well.
Well, I think it's hate...
...love.
I hate...
...love you very much, Jarrett Roy.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
I just been s-so busy
putting up walls and making lists
and throwing myself into work
so this wouldn't happen.
I am...
terrified of another person
holding my heart in their hands.
But when I got what I wanted...
...it didn't feel like I thought it would.
Because success just isn't enough.
Not without someone I...
hate/love to share it with.
[clicks tongue]
Mahogany.
Nice.
You were right.
About the book, about the story, about us.
I see you're the man for me, and I just...
I really hope I'm not too late.
You could've stopped at "You were right."
[uplifting music playing]
Hate/love?
I can work with that.
-Oh, shoot. I...
-[clears throat]
-I still got to catch my flight...
-Okay.
...turn down the job with the people
at Audible, you know?
Yeah. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-You are worth it.
-[♪ Salt-N-Pepa sings
"Whatta Man - Rerecorded"]
♪
Oh, all right...
Fly safe. And then come back to me.
♪
What a man, what a man, what a man
-♪
what a mighty good man
♪
-♪
Uh, all right
♪
Gotta say it again, now
♪♪
You have never looked more beautiful.
And I'm not just saying that
'cause I did your makeup.
[both laugh]
[gasps]
-Truly.
-[sighs]
You look so stunning.
And we're so happy for you.
[Brenda chuckles]
Thank you both for everything.
I love you girls so much.
-Don't do that. Don't do that.
-[sighs]
I can't mess up my face.
-Oh, my God, are you crying?
-No.
No. No.
-I'm getting married!
-You're getting married!
[laughing]
[Michael]
We are gathered here today
in the sight of God
to join these two very special people
together in holy matrimony.
We celebrate two hearts
who have put God
at the center of their relationship,
two people who have done the hard work
and broken old patterns.
Today is the beginning
of a brand-new journey,
where it's you, him, God
against the world.
[dog barks]
[guests aahing, chuckling]
Brenda, Ayden,
when we see you,
we see real relationship goals.
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
-You better kiss your bride, brother.
-[Brenda laughing]
Come here. Get over here.
[cheering and applause]
Whoo!
-[screaming excitedly]
-[laughing]
[♪ Keyshia Cole sings "Love"]
[both singing along] ♪
Whoa, love
♪
Never knew what I was missing
but I knew once we start kissing
♪
I found
[laughing]
♪
love
Never knew what I was missing
♪
but I knew once we start kissing
I found
♪
Uh-huh.
you
♪♪
-[Jarrett] Yeah. Mm.
-[Leah sighs, chuckles]
-[♪ Kelly Rowland and Method Man
sing "Complicated"]
-♪
Been a couple months
♪
and I been feeling feelings,
but don't wanna jump the gun
♪
'cause I don't wanna assess the vibes
But I'm easy, right? That's a lie
♪
I been dying just to make you mine,
but, bae, give me a sign
♪
Games are freaking lame,
and I don't really want to play them
♪
at the mercy of you
If I'm honest, I would rather us
to focus on what matters
♪
'cause I don't wanna lose you
Baby, why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪
Oh, oh
Baby, it'd be better if we could
just have a conversation
♪
♪ ...
tion
♪
-♪
You wanna argue, argue with who?
♪
-♪
You wanna argue, who?
♪
-♪
I just wanna love you
♪
-♪
I just wanna love you
♪
-♪
It's all I wanna do
♪
-♪
Whoo
♪
Baby, why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪
Life's complicated
but not as hard as we made it
♪
If life's a B, then she's jaded,
that lady nothin' to play with
♪
And she my A-list,
the only play in my playlist
♪
to keep it cool and composed
like a modern-day Amadeus
♪
Love us or hate us,
we're blessed and highly favored
♪
My guess is we on the clock,
I am one of her favorite flavors
♪
like I'm shootin' my shot
and I'm one of her favorite players
♪
Plus the johnson is magic
like one of her favorite Lakers
♪
So wait up, I ain't tryin' to argue,
but maybe later
♪
I'm trying to cater and Spotify you
with baby makers
♪
Caught in the rapture,
Anita Baker, let Johnny Blaze ya
♪
Sex in the city to kill the kitty
like euthanasia
♪
Work's been a trip,
got a lot on my chest, mm-mm
♪
I swear to God I've been doing my best,
mm-mm
♪
You try to help,
try to come to my rescue
♪
It's still a mess,
but I'm happy I met you
♪
Black roses in my yard
because you water my garden
♪
-♪
garden
♪
-♪
Uh
♪
Cold shooter, doot-doot-doot,
got me right where my heart is
♪
Ooh
Oh, baby, why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪
Oh, oh
Oh, baby, it'd be better
if we could just have a conversation
♪
...tion
-♪
You wanna argue, argue with who?
♪
-♪
You wanna argue, who?
♪
-♪
I just wanna love you
♪
-♪
I just wanna love you
♪
-♪
It's all I wanna do
♪
-♪
Whoo
♪
Baby, why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪
Oh
It don't really matter
if it's hard for us to balance
♪
'cause my heart beats for you
If I'm honest, I would rather us
to focus on what matters
♪
'cause I don't wanna lose you
Baby, why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪
Oh, oh
Oh, baby, it'd be better
if we could just have a conversation
♪
...tion
-♪
You wanna argue, argue with who?
♪
-♪
You wanna argue, who?
♪
-♪
I just wanna love you
♪
-♪
I just wanna love you
♪
-♪
It's all I wanna do
♪
-♪
Whoo
♪
Baby, why you gotta go
and make it complicated?
♪♪
[Plies]
You wanna argue.
[chuckles]
I can't argue with you.
No!
You mad.
Look at you.
You big mad.
[chuckles]
[song ends]
[lighthearted music playing]
♪ ♪
[music ends]