Come on!
Time for bed!
Let's go to sleep!
-Yes. -Oh, no!
Go to sleep.
Have you washed your face yet?
Yeah.
No.
A story! A story!
And!
¡Shh!
A long time ago there lived a brave and noble princess named Peach.
She was the great protector of the Mushroom Kingdom.
Their story begins many years ago.
I want to hear the plumbers' story.
I already told you that story last night, the previous one...
also and the previous one as well.
Plumbers, plumbers, plumbers, plumbers, plumbers, plumbers, plumbers, plumbers,
plumbers.
Ok.
This is a brotherly thing.
Mario and Luigi…
Read the Donkey Kong part.
¡Donkey Kong!
¡Donkey...
Let's leave the rest for tomorrow.
Now everyone to bed, okay?
Wait, I won't be long.
Princess Rosalina!
You will come with me!
¡No!
- You messed with the equiv... Princess - Mom!
I had a bad dream.
There was no dream.
From the ashes of his father's defeat, a new conqueror rises!
They will fear the name of Bowser once more!
Oh, will you be quiet?
But I'm so happy for you and your...
First princess kidnapped!
Not with my mommy!
SUPER MARIO GALAXY THE MOVIE www.LatinoMegaHD.net
How's it going, huh?
That jump was incredible, bro!
Mario, well now we're famous motorcyclists, aren't we?
Of course.
Oh!
They've arrived!
Ok.
Which pipe broke now?
Ok, ok.
What if they point it out to us?
Okay, I think we'll follow that terrifying sound.
Calm down!
You're not the same old cowardly crybaby you used to be!
Yes, I am!
People don't change!
That's the problem.
Hello.
Don't be scared.
Get out of there.
Okay, ya.
Quiet.
What's your name, little one?
¡Yoshi!
It's a pleasure, Yoshi!
And how did you end up in that pipe?
¡Oh!
Get out of the way!
I don't think we'll ever know.
I don't care!
Herein lies the problem!
¡Hola, mi Yoshi!
In the end, it was all because of a Yoshi!
Yeah!
When we found that little boy, he...
Where did he go?
He seemed nice, didn't you think?
Hey, he does know it's my motorcycle, right?
Where are you leading us?
Try to enjoy it, princess.
It's the last place you'll ever see alive!
It's great, right?
I know my dad will love it.
Mommy, I'm scared!
Everything is going to be alright.
What in the Cave.
Who brought a princess?
Yeah!
And I didn't bring just any princess.
She is the guardian of the cosmos.
The mother of stars!
With their powers, we're going to destroy the universe!
She will give her life for our glory!
Yeah!
It was a good speech, wasn't it?
It was direct and descriptive.
Nobody touches my children!
¡Corre!
The greatest battle of my life is approaching!
The time has come to free my father!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, PRINCESS PEACH
Do you think he'll like it?
Mario, do you feel something special for the princess?
That?
How can they think one can't give it to...
The perfect gift for your friend...
...so that he can see how much he cares?
If the moon that's like a pizza appeals to you...
a Peach.
Didn't I fall in love with Peach?
Let's go.
Yeah!
Say, Mushroom!
Hello hello!
Hello, Toad!
You look amazing.
And who is this?
¿Yoshi?
Nobody can resist this cute face.
Come on!
The dinosaur suddenly appears and is now part of the group.
Hey, have you seen the princess?
Peach, you're missing your own party.
I hate birthdays.
Yes. Luigi spent his tenth birthday crying.
He said his childhood was over.
The funny thing about all this is that today isn't really my birthday.
Today the Toads found me as a child.
None of them have any idea where I come from.
All my life I've wanted to know where he is...
my whole family.
It must be hard for you.
Sometimes I feel so lost.
Since it's not your birthday, I assume you don't want any presents.
¡Mario!
Okay, it hurt.
I love it!
Look!
¡Mira!
Princess Peach, I finally found you.
Are you feeling better now?
I can't believe that's you.
Mom read us many bedtime stories about you.
About me?
Are you sure?
He said that if anything ever happened to him,
We would look for you and you would help us.
Princess!
My mom was kidnapped!
But what happened?
A robot takes her to an ugly planet.
Beyond the Galaxy, Celestial Gate.
Will you help us?
Peach, sorry.
I tried to...
Yes, yes, we were spying, so what?
Don't even think about leaving!
Hey, can you give the princess a minute?
She has everything under control.
I disagree, Mario.
Even though my pajamas say I'm your fan.
There's nothing to know because she's not leaving.
Okay, everyone outside.
We'll discuss it in the morning.
Rest, princess.
Toad, pack our things.
What do you mean he left?
Yes, Mario left you this.
Dear Mustache, I went to the Celestial Gate galaxy...
to find the mother of this little girl.
I leave the kingdom in your hands.
Honestly, Peach.
Sincerely?
Oh la la, that's a good sign!
Has Princess Peach left?
Oh, no!
Please calm down!
The Super Mario Brothers will be in charge of the kingdom temporarily.
Ah, now what?
Hey buddy!
You scared me!
What, did you want to see us?
Stay there, I'll be right up.
Time to absorb!
Clean the paint!
And trim this bonsai!
Here I go!
Hello, Luigi!
Hello, Mario.
Admire!
I've created a masterpiece for Princess Peach!
How's it going, huh?
Be completely honest.
Wow, those are beautiful colors.
Since you want my opinion, it's garbage.
How dare you look at my masterpiece and say that?
Do you think painting is easy?
I'm going to rip the skin off your bones!
Excuse me, it's old Bowser talking.
I'm still confronting my demons.
Okay, I feel better now.
As I was saying, it's not just a gift,
It is a peace offering.
I will ask him to release me, not for good behavior...
For amazing behavior!
Free yourself, forget it.
And let's not even talk about him making you big again.
Even though I'm fully rehabilitated?
Mario, if he's a different person now.
In addition, we have a book club every week.
Yes, I'll bring the soup.
I don't trust you, monster.
And especially not the princess.
Either you start trusting me, or I'm going to rip your eyes out...
Sorry, I didn't mean that...
Okay, I won't bother you anymore.
I'm going to go and rest.
I need my eight hours of sleep, or seriously, I'll turn into a monster.
Have a good rest!
In the name of the Koopas, I order you to release my father.
Over my dead body.
So be it.
Why don't we start again?
And we all introduced ourselves.
Okay, hi, I'm Luigi.
I am Bowser Jr. and I've come to take my father away.
Now!
No.
He was doing very well, but I came to give him a hand.
That?
Dad!
Is everyone okay?
Where are we?
Sweet freedom!
Oh no, it's a joke!
Goodbye, idiots!
Don't even think about running!
¡No!
You can't catch the wind!
That's exactly what I did.
It was a metaphor!
Let go!
Spit it out, it's going to hurt you.
That was intense!
I know, I feel really sorry for you.
I'm still a mini work in progress.
Excuse me, okay?
And you expect me to shake hands with the turtle whose son tried to kill me?
My son?
I haven't seen my son in years.
Mario, I've been a terrible father.
He must hate me.
Hate you?
Your son tried to cut off my head to free you!
He wants to see you.
Perhaps, I don't know, he needs someone to guide him.
Really?
Do you think I still have a chance to reconnect with my boy?
See, Mario?
It is connected to his feelings.
I'm drowning in them, Mario!
Okay, let's keep walking.
We need to figure out how to get off the planet and find Peach.
¡Toad!
There it is!
The Celestial Gateway Galaxy!
Welcome to the Celestial Gate Galaxy.
Your Celestial Gateway to the galaxies.
Toad,
Where are you going?
She's the one we're looking for!
MISSING PRINCESS ROSALINA
Princess?
Are you OK?
Did a Kiki get lost?
Have you seen Kiki's friends?
Poor little lost monkey!
¡Ya, ya!
I'll take care of you!
That monkey!
He uses his cuteness to steal!
Toad, wait!
Bring our boosters and coins!
And my unfinished novel!
Permission!
Sorry!
Excuse me!
It's ours now!
The monkey went through the wall!
Don't go away.
Hey, you!
Monkey of...
Give me back my backpack.
SCANNING IN PROGRESS
Dad, I know you're out there somewhere.
Sir, it's a lost cause.
What matters most in our time of pain and sorrow is...
Let's give each other strength!
Hey, calm down, old man!
We have to keep looking for my dad!
Mario, Bowser wants to talk to you for a moment.
You know, Mario?
Every child thinks that their father is the greatest thing in the world.
I don't want to disappoint my son by seeing me so small.
I'm not going to make you big.
You have always lived a small life.
But I was born to be great!
Undo the power of the Blue Mushroom!
And I swear to fight by your side for all eternity!
It's a great deal!
Eternity is a long time!
That's how we'll be unstoppable!
No.
Go ahead, hit me, Mario!
¡Pégame!
Yes, Mario, hit him.
We can trust him.
¡Pégame!
Come on, don't be afraid!
¡Dale!
Hit me now!
Pathetic and failed attempt at a plumber!
You won't regret it!
What are we waiting for?
There's a castle over there!
Come on!
Follow me!
Princess, look!
Kiki, you brought something very good.
Princesses are quite valuable.
Kiki says your novel sucks!
Why is it that princesses always let themselves be captured?
Tell us what you know about the lost princess!
I don't know anything!
Listen to me carefully, you wart-faced bastard!
You're going to tell me where to find Rosalina!
Or what?
Oh, princess!
That's going to cost you dearly!
And!
Where is it?
Did I look like a snitch to you?
Oh yes, I have it!
Last chance!
¡Ok, ok!
Listen to me!
Bowser's son has it!
Where?
In the nebula galaxy!
¡Toad!
Give me that!
Call Bowser Jr. Now!
Move those little paws, puppy!
Hello.
We are looking for a way to leave their planet.
They have to talk to the queen, but the lizard-faced one stays here.
I'll fix this.
Greetings, Your Highness!
We are trying to reach the Celestial Gate galaxy...
They're the aliens who destroyed my flower field!
Learn them!
Take them to the honey mines!
No, not if I can help it!
Well, someone has to pay for their crimes.
Arrest me!
I will serve his sentence in his place!
I can do the work of a hundred men and eat the food of about ten thousand bees!
Lock me up and let them go to Heaven's Gate!
We have a deal!
Take them to the gates of heaven!
Are you sure, Bowser?
You're not as horrible as I thought.
Thank you.
Give me a hug!
Take good care of it, okay?
I always do that!
This miserable insect will help them get through!
Bye bye!
Make your enemy proud!
When I'm free, my sweetheart and I will go out dancing until the sun comes up.
Do you have a sweetheart at home?
He abandoned me at the altar and that hardened my black heart.
Today I try to heal, remembering who I was before his love.
You are a sensitive soul.
That?
Be strong!
The right one for you will come along!
¡Oh!
Hi, Dad.
¿Junior?
My little one!
Look how much you've grown!
And all this is yours?
Hey, shouldn't you be at boarding school?
The boarding school?
More like boring, because I was expelled.
You grew into a real man while I wasn't looking, son.
Dad!
We're both going to become the most powerful guys in the universe!
Do you remember when I was a little turtle?
You worked so hard to conquer the world!
But every now and then you took a break...
And you would tuck me in and tell me our favorite story.
Those were the best nights of my entire life!
Tell me the story!
Again?
Long ago, there was a powerful villain with shining hair.
He conquered everything in his path.
And that villain had a son.
The two of them traveled the universe eager to find a home.
But every place they went was super...
bored.
Bored!
And they created their own planet!
Admire!
Bowser's Planet!
The sinister sanctuary where they would live out the rest of their days.
With a roller coaster of evil.
A gorge with lava.
And a mountain they carved in the shape of their heads.
And at the top of the planet, they built the biggest canyon of all.
He could destroy the entire universe!
Did they call him?
Apocalyptic canyon!
To get it moving, they needed...
The most powerful princess in the universe!
And once they extracted all its power,
And the weapon was ready...
They traveled from planet to planet, destroying everything...
the one who had disrespected them.
¡Boom!
Until they danced on the ashes of the universe, like supreme kings!
The end.
Will you tell me tomorrow night, Daddy?
Of course.
Rest, my little one.
Well!
I finally built the planet!
Did you do it?
We're traveling to it!
Together, Dad!
¡Dos Bowsers!
Unlimited!
My lords, we have a little problem.
Welcome to the information center.
My name is Rob.
Do you need information?
We need a pilot.
It's urgent.
With pleasure.
The pilots are on the flight deck,
which is located right...
Oh, Rob!
You're killing me!
I'm sorry.
I don't want to kill you.
¡Toad!
I'm Rob.
I know!
GOOD.
Thank you for visiting this center.
Where is the cover?
This...
-...here. - Thank you!
You are welcome.
I can't believe it!
Hello!
Would you take us to the Nebula Galaxy, sir?
No.
Excuse me, how much to take us to the Nebula Galaxy?
Very dangerous for this cute pilot!
Okay, explain it to me.
Why would a princess try to go to the most dangerous place in the galaxy?
Who are you?
Don't ask me personal questions.
Oh, forgive me, I didn't mean to...
¡Soy Fox McCloud!
Leader of the legendary team, Star Fox!
Only three things matter to me.
Keeping the Lylat system safe,
fighting alongside my friends and doing extreme barrel rolls.
I mean, barrel rolls, dudes!
But one day, my Warp Drive exploded.
It tore a giant hole in the tissue of the...
time and space and it absorbed me into another universe.
That's what I get for having a frog as an engineer.
Now I travel the galaxy in search of a way home.
Doing good, if they can afford me.
Oh, and I also have some super cool boots.
Now that's a good origin story...
Who is going to take us to the Nebula Galaxy?
Did I look desperate, like I was starving?
Okay, deal.
I'll refuel the Air Wing and we'll be off in five, gentlemen.
That's the coolest guy I've ever seen!
Mario, I have a great idea.
When you see Peach, go up to her and say, oh,
blah, blah, blah.
Oh, hi, how are you?
And then, boom!, you ask her out on a date.
I don't know, Lu.
Would a princess go on a date with a plumber?
Mario would be the luckiest princess in the world...
if she were your girlfriend.
I know she's going to say yes.
And you're going to ask her if she has a friend for me.
Now, we just have to find her.
That's fair, because...
¡Peach!
¿Mario?
Ah, train a Yoshi.
¡Mario!
So what?
Shaking hands is cool, I mean...
Shaking hands is cool, I thought you'd like it...
Because it's cool.
¡Mario!
I discovered where Rosalina is.
And he said he's going to take us.
Beautiful ship!
Nice mustache.
Come one, come all!
It's the life of a space rebel!
I don't see him as that rebellious, he's like Mrs. Cacelato's dog.
And does Mrs. Cacelato's dog do this?
I like this handsome guy!
AIM
You'd better hold on to whatever you can!
Olé!
Grrr!
They're going to pay for that!
Wait!
¡Junior!
I've already lived with them!
They're pathetic, but it makes me sad to kill them!
Are you saying it's better if we don't kill them?
That's strange...
¡Ok!
I'm doing this for you, Dad!
When I'm done with them, they'll be begging for their mommies!
And what does that do, Junior?
Bowser!
He saw through our faces!
Oh!
He made them babies!
Don't worry, Dad.
By this time tomorrow, you'll have forgotten all about those slimy guys in overalls.
The whole universe is going to be ours!
Is it working now?
No.
Toad, the babies.
That?
I'm coming!
Come here!
¡Yoshi!
Come back!
¡Luigi!
Kid, get down from there!
¡Mario!
¡Yoshi!
No. Let it go, it's not a toy!
Let it go, give it to me!
Let her go, kid!
Honestly, I did enjoy being a baby, the ideas...
The terrifying things that haunted me disappeared, it was nice.
We're going to make you feel like new, okay?
You'll be fine, it's just a scratch.
It's a scratch!
¡Oh no!
Don't worry, we'll find a way to get off the planet.
Mario, we're galaxies away from Rosalina, the ship...
There's no way around it, and the strangest thing is, we have another dinosaur!
I know you're frustrated.
Princesses don't get frustrated!
Okay, so can I not be frustrated with you?
Okay, testing, testing, here Green, Stop, Red,
Chaparro and Sorron, dog.
We request an immediate evacuation.
We crashed in the middle of Dinoland.
We're bringing a royal cargo...
Leave him alone!
Let's watch it!
This is what happens when they don't go to sleep on time.
Mayday Mayday, Luigi the Fabulous is signing off, over and out!
¡LUIIIIGIIIIIIIII!
Their mustaches were ridiculous, but they weren't bad people.
They were your friends, weren't they?
Nothing is more dangerous than a friend!
When you let your guard down, you get stabbed in the back.
Where did you hear that?
That's what you told me when you took me to my first day of school.
- Yes, I'm a good father. - Those friends of yours wanted to ruin you.
Becoming something you are not.
Do you know who won't hurt you?
Your family. Family is forever.
Close your eyes.
Dad!
Don't cheat.
Now open them.
Hey!
An extremely rare object is coming this way.
Here we go!
We'll reach the nebula galaxy before the party!
A long time ago there lived a brave and noble princess named Peach.
Their story begins many years ago.
When she lived on a small planet with her sister Rosalina.
Both were made of stardust.
Their love burned as brightly as the stars themselves.
Together they could invoke the power of the cosmos.
But the forces of evil wanted to obtain that power.
Rosalina had to send Peach away,
to a safe place.
The Toads raised and protected her, until she was strong enough to protect them.
Dad!
Welcome to Bowser's planet!
Did you build the planet all by yourself?
But that's not all!
We have our very own apocalyptic cannon!
And the princess I kidnapped to enhance it!
The universe will never forgive them!
This is who you are!
This is where you belong!
Tonight we will destroy the Mushroom Kingdom!
And tomorrow, the universe!
Bowser!
Yes, long live the king!
They're waiting for your return!
Sometimes you can lose your way on life's rainbow path.
But hopefully!
A mini version of yourself helps you remember your true nature.
What's in the Cave?
Your king has returned!
We'll bring them down to the planet!
Get ready, things are about to get crazy!
Team Star Fox! Ready!
And!
¡Agarrense!
Something's coming!
Do your thing, McCloud.
And!
Good luck!
I don't know what it means!
Let them go that way and we'll stay this way!
Ah, I understand now!
¡Oh!
Intruder alert!
Catch them!
Just a little more and that's it, dude!
My lords!
The tormentors have returned!
Let me handle it!
Build a top-level security system.
They're going to be torn to pieces!
I love being your dad!
Oh, and the days are long, but the years are short!
Hello, Pichimario!
Get ready to see your creator!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Now I have them!
I'm not going to let them ruin your plan, son!
Bowser!
It didn't have to end like this!
I know there's still a little goodness left in you!
Let us through!
Now!
Or what?
Are they going to humiliate me at my wedding?
Shrink up like an insect and get into a jar?
Should I join a book club, too?
We had a great time, Mario!
But Bowser is back!
And they will feel my full fury!
Dad!
I am the lord of bones!
I am the skeleton king!
And I am his son!
¡Mario!
¡Corre!
¡Scarf!
Yes, yes, yes!
¡Yoshi!
How odd!
Stop this, Lu!
- Lu! - What?
You already know I'm not good at drawing!
And!
In the name of the Koopas!
Son!
Dad!
Help me!
¡Junior!
- Dad! - My boy!
Rosalina!
I need you to try!
I knew you would come for me.
¡Mira!
I found your femur, Dad!
You're okay, Junior.
Let's find my foot.
¡Mario!
She's my sister, Rosalina!
It's great that they finally found each other.
Oh, I love it when families get together!
Mother?
Mother!
My babies!
We miss you so much!
I missed them a lot too.
Mommy, can we visit the Mushroom Kingdom?
I want to see the castle!
OK that's fine.
Hey, what about the castle?
Ah, well, the castle, that castle, ah...
He died!
And what does that mean?
Let me tell you something?
We are going to rebuild.
The best castle of all!
Who wants to help?
Oh, yes!
SUPER MARIO GALAXY THE MOVIE
What's your next stop?
That lovely space princess repaired my warp drive...
And I'm going home.
Good luck with them!
They are a rather peculiar family.
Patience, son.
No prison will hold us.
We'll be leaving soon.
Hello, lizards.
Are they trying to escape?
Are they going to obey my rules?
Don't go away, son.
It won't break us.
Body first, bones later.
And only dust remains.
Stop now!
Be quiet!
They cannot silence the truth.
They make it noisier.
Like the drums that foretell...
Death!
Oh, ya, ya.
What's wrong, little monkey?
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, thank you so much!
YOUR HIGHNESS!